You can't be afraid to verbalize your
你不能害怕承认自己的
ignorance. That's holding you back.
无知。 那是阻碍你前进的因素。
&gt;&gt; Give me an example.
请举个例子。
&gt;&gt; I can give you several like investing.
我可以给你举几个投资方面的例子。   就
Like you're telling me that if I put
好像你在告诉我，如果我
this money in here right now, I get 30x
现在把这笔钱放进去，就能得到 30 倍
20x. What the a scam? I know a scam.
20 倍的回报。 这是骗局吗？ 我知道这是个骗局。
When I see one, go find you another
等我看到一个傻瓜，你就去找另一个
idiot cuz it ain't happening over here,
傻瓜吧，因为这种事在这里不可能发生，
buddy. But when you go, you say, "I
伙计。 但当你真正去了解之后，你会说：“我
don't know what that means. How does
不知道那是什么意思。
investing really work? I don't know
投资到底是怎么运作的？我不知道该去
where to get it." Now you're a part of
哪里学习。” 现在你参与到了
the right conversations. You're part of
正确的对话中。 你拥有
the right opportunities, but you get
绝佳的机会，但你却
there by being the dummy in them. And
因为在这些机会中扮演傻瓜的角色而获得这些机会。
now look at what I'm able to do.
现在看看我能做到什么。
&gt;&gt; Kevin,
凯文，
I love it. I love it.
我太喜欢了。 我喜欢它。
&gt;&gt; Kevin, it took 13 years from where you
凯文，从你
did your first stand up to you having
第一次表演脱口秀到你迎来高光
your moment. But why didn't you quit?
时刻，花了13年时间。 但你为什么不辞职呢？
&gt;&gt; Because of the lessons that my mom gave
因为我妈妈从小就教导我，而
from being [music] very scarred from my
我的哥哥给我留下了很深的心理创伤（音乐）
brother. So, let's go back. I grew up in
。 那么，我们回去吧。 我是在
North Philadelphia. My brother sold the
费城北部长大的。 我哥哥卖
drugs. My dad was always in jail, out of
毒品。 我爸爸总是进出
jail. My mom wasn't going to let that
监狱。 我妈妈绝不会让
happen with me. So, we had an agreement.
我遭遇那种事。 所以，我们达成了协议。
I had a certain amount of time to make
我只有一定的时间来创作
comedy work. [music] And in my mind, it
喜剧作品。  [音乐] 在我看来，这不会
wasn't going to be hard because there
很难，因为
was no other option. I would figure it
没有其他选择。 我会想办法的
out. So, I was driving from Philadelphia
。 所以，我当时每天都要从费城开车
to New York every day. I wasn't coming
去纽约。
home until 4:00 a.m. where I was doing
我
25 to 28 sets a weekend.
周末要练 25 到 28 组，凌晨 4 点才能回家。
I worked at for a very, very long time.
我在那里工作了很长时间。
And the struggle left you with days of
而这种挣扎之后，你常常会感到迷茫，不知道
what am I doing? Can I [music] pay my
自己到底在做什么。 我能靠音乐支付
rent? This man, but my mom's biggest
房租吗？ 这个人，但我妈妈教给我最重要的一
lesson was you're not quitting. And not
课是：你不能放弃。 没
many people are going to do the 13 years
多少人愿意经历这13年的
of hard. Most people opt out at year two
艰苦学习。 大多数人会在第二年选择退出，
and want to go find a quick return.
并希望寻找快速回报的机会。
Well, you keep quitting to start
你总是放弃，然后开始做
something else that you think is the
你认为才是
idea. It's just a cycle. You're never
正确的事情。 这只是一个循环。 你永远也
completing anything. You got to make a
完成不了任何事。 你必须
choice of the thing you're going to do
选择你要做的事情，
and finish. I made the choice that
然后把它完成。 我决定要把
standup comedy was what I was going to
单口喜剧作为我的
finish. Because if I focused and did it
最终目标。 因为如果我集中精力把这件事做好
well, that would open up the doors for
，那就会为
me to do everything else [music] that I
我打开通往其他所有我
want to do.
想做的音乐事业的大门。
&gt;&gt; But they say that you can't have
但他们说，
everything in life.
人生不可能事事如意。
&gt;&gt; So, what is the cost? Have you struggled
那么，成本是多少？ 你是否曾受过
with your mental health? What advice
心理健康方面的困扰？
have you got for young men in terms of
对于年轻男性，你有什么建议可以帮助他们
like what it takes to be a good man?
成为一个好男人？   现在的情况很
&gt;&gt; It's a weird thing that's happening
奇怪，
where the definition of a good man is so
好男人的定义变得如此
foggy. It seems that in this time today
模糊不清。 如今，似乎有
more men are being forward [music]
更多男性在音乐方面走在前列，
wanting to express and talk but the fear
想要表达和倾诉，但又害怕
of being judged [music] after.
事后被评判。
&gt;&gt; Do you have that fear?
你有这种恐惧吗？
I see messages all the time in the
我经常在
comments section that some of you didn't
评论区看到有人留言说他们没有
realize you didn't subscribe. So, if you
意识到自己没有订阅。 所以，如果您
could do me a favor and double check if
能帮我个忙，再次确认一下
you're a subscriber to this channel,
您是否是本频道的订阅者，我
that would be tremendously appreciated.
将万分感激。
It's the simple, it's the free thing
这是件简单又免费的事情，
that anybody that watches this show
任何经常观看本节目的人都
frequently can do to help us here to
可以做，以帮助我们
keep everything going in this show in
保持本节目目前的良好发展
the trajectory it's on. So, please do
势头。 所以，请您
double check if you've subscribed and uh
再次确认是否已订阅，
thank you so much because in a strange
非常感谢，因为从某种意义上说
way, you are you're part of our history
，您是我们历史的一部分，
and you're on this journey with us and I
您与我们一起踏上了这段旅程，我
appreciate you for that. So yeah, thank
为此感谢您。 是的，
you. [music]
谢谢。  [音乐]
In so many ways, you're clearly an
从很多方面来看，你显然是个
anomaly. For you to be the way that you
异类。 要想成为现在的你
are, there must be some kind of early
，一定有一些早期的
context that people need to be aware of,
背景因素需要人们了解，
a certain wiring or a cauldron that has
某种特定的思维模式或环境因素
has sort of shaped you into who you are.
塑造了你，使你成为现在的你。
What is that context that I need to
我需要了解的背景是什么
understand?
？
&gt;&gt; I am a very driven individual and I'm
我是一个非常有干劲的人，我的
driven off of ideiation. I I like the
动力来自于构思。 我喜欢
fact that you can have thoughts and if
你可以拥有各种想法，如果
you're in love with the thoughts that
你喜欢
you're having, you can be energized to
你正在思考的想法，你就可以充满活力地
bring those thoughts like into a bigger
将这些想法变成更大的
reality. That's like that's the real
现实。 那对
fuel to the brain for me.
我来说就像是大脑真正的燃料。
&gt;&gt; Do you think at the at the very core of
你认为在
you that's what's motivating you because
你内心深处，这就是你的动力所在吗？因为这
&gt;&gt; absolutely
绝对
&gt;&gt; that's like a process but the the
是一个过程，但其
outcome of that is success in all its
结果就是各种
forms. It's material success
形式的成功。 这是物质上的成功
&gt;&gt; or failure. I mean like there is no
或失败。 我的意思是，没有
success without failure. They go hand in
失败就没有成功。 它们
hand. And with the failure comes amazing
相辅相成。 失败带来宝贵的经验
lessons, adjustments
教训和调整，让
and you get sharper because of the [__]
你变得更加敏锐，因为
that you've done wrong or that you
你做错了一些事情，或者你以前
didn't know to approach a certain way
不知道如何处理某些事情，而
that you now know how to approach. So I
现在你知道该如何处理了。 所以我
embrace the concept of failure just as
欣然接受失败，就像
much as I embrace the win of success.
欣然接受成功一样。
Had I met you at 10 years old or 15
如果我在你 10 岁或 15 岁时遇见你
years old,
，
how similar would you have looked in?
你现在的样子会和现在有多相似？
&gt;&gt; Not even close.
差远了。
&gt;&gt; Not even close. Not motivated to do the
差远了。 没有动力去做
things that I didn't want to do. Uh not
我不想做的事情。 呃，我不是
a good student, kind of [__] off
个好学生，有点逃学
school, the opportunities that come with
，错过了学校带来的机会
school, the extracurricular activities
，错过了那些
that I didn't want to do that I was
我不想参加但
doing that my mom made me do. Hanging
妈妈逼我参加的课外活动。 一起闲逛
out was the thing. Hanging out was the
才是最重要的。 闲逛是一种
luxury. It was the fun. And it's it
奢侈。 乐趣就在于此。 而且它
wasn't available. My mom was strict. So,
还不可用。 我妈妈很严厉。 所以，
I didn't have the luxury of doing all
我没有条件去做所有
those things, which is why I wanted them
这些事情，正因如此，我才更加渴望它们
more.
。
&gt;&gt; I found this photo of your mother.
我找到了你母亲的这张照片。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Me and Nancy Hart.
。 我和南希·哈特。
&gt;&gt; She was strict.
她很严厉。
&gt;&gt; Very strict with me. Uh my older
对我非常严格。 呃，我的
brother, he had the, you know, he had he
哥哥，你知道，他比较
had a little more lenency. He he freed
宽容一些。 他把他放了
him, you know, he curfew late at night.
，你知道，他晚上很晚才实行宵禁。
But my brother did all the all of the
但其他所有的事情都是我哥哥做的
other stuff. My brother sold the drugs,
。 我哥哥贩毒，
you know,
你知道，他
crime and and stupid [__] as a teenager
十几岁的时候就做过一些小罪小恶的事，连
to her own mom felt like she wasn't
他妈妈都觉得她不会让
going to let that happen with me. So,
我重蹈覆辙。 所以，
um because of the mistakes she saw that
因为她看到了
she made with my brother.
自己对我哥哥犯下的错误，她对他更加保护了。
&gt;&gt; You see what I'm saying? So, I got the I
你明白我的意思吗？ 所以，我运气不好，吃了亏
got the short end of the stick.
。
&gt;&gt; So, I didn't have the curfew. I didn't I
所以，我没有宵禁。 我
wasn't able to go hang out. I wasn't
没能出去玩。 我没
able to do all those things. That's why
能做到所有这些事情。 这就是
I wanted that so much. So I rebelled in
我如此渴望它的原因。 所以，在必须这样做的时候，我进行了反抗，
I was like, "Well, you don't let me do
我说：“好吧，你们不让我
this, so I don't
这样做，所以我也不这样做，
&gt;&gt; I don't want to do this." So I kind of
我不想这样做。” 所以我
[__] off a lot of those opportunities.
错失了很多机会。
And your father,
还有你父亲，
&gt;&gt; Henry Witherspoon, Spoon G's, my guy.
亨利·威瑟斯彭，Spoon G's 的老板，我的兄弟。
Uh, you know, a [__] up in the eyes of
呃，你知道，在大多数人眼里他是个失败者
most, but
，但
my my dad, you know, he didn't
我爸爸，你知道，他
necessarily do the right things in life.
一生中未必做了正确的事。
Um,
嗯，
gang, crime, all of the [__] Jail, in
帮派、犯罪，所有那些乱七八糟的东西。 监狱，
jail, out of jail, drugs. Uh
入狱，出狱，毒品。 呃，
I mean that that environment that we
我的意思是，我们成长的环境可能对
the best environment for for anyone but
任何人来说都不是最好的环境，但对
those that live in it because it's all
生活在其中的人来说，那是一个很棒的环境，因为那是
we know and the normaly is the low. My
我们所知道的一切，而正常情况是低水平的。 我
mom strive for the higher side of it. My
妈妈力求做到最好。 我
mom was education uh degree, trying to
妈妈一直在努力提升自己
always wanting to get better, always
，不断学习，
wanting to educate herself more because
因为
she felt that it was the biggest
她觉得这是除了她自己之外没有人
strength that nobody could control but
能掌控的最大力量
her.
。
&gt;&gt; And they separated.
他们分开了。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. They were never never married.
。 他们从未结婚。
&gt;&gt; Never married.
未婚。
&gt;&gt; And did they physically separate at a
他们是否在某个时间点真正分开过
certain point? I mean, I think my dad my
？ 我的意思是，我觉得我
dad only lived in the house with me like
爸爸只在
my really younger years. Like maybe from
我很小的时候和我一起住过。 大概
five to seven,
五到七岁，
maybe eight if I can remember. Like I
如果我没记错的话，也许是八岁。 就像我从小就
didn't have I didn't grow up with like
没有爸爸一样，没有和
my dad home, you know? So when my mom
爸爸一起生活，你知道吗？ 所以当我妈说：
was like, "Fuck that. You're out of
“去他妈的，你给我滚出去
here." It was over. like he my dad he
。” 结束了。 就像我爸爸一样，他以前
was a weekend dad or every other weekend
是周末爸爸，或者隔周周末
dad or you know during the week stopped
爸爸，或者你知道，平时他会过来看看，
by then he was in and out of jail then
后来他经常进出监狱，后来
we got on drugs we didn't see him at
我们开始吸毒，就再也没见过他了
all.
。
&gt;&gt; How did you understand that as a kid?
你小时候是怎么理解这个概念的？
Like how does a kid understand the the
孩子怎么能理解
dad coming and going being in jail
爸爸因为吸毒进出监狱呢
drugs?
？
&gt;&gt; You are
你是
a product of your environment and in
环境的产物，在
that environment that's the norm. So
那种环境下，这就是常态。 所以，
when you so when you say like how did
当你这么说的时候，
you understand that? Well, nobody had a
你是怎么理解的？ 嗯，他们都没有
dad.
父亲。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; Right. Like all all my friends, our
正确的。 就像我所有的朋友一样，我们的
dads, like we see him when we see him
爸爸，我们每次见到他都会
and we love him because that's what we
爱他，因为
that's what we thought that it should
我们认为他应该是这样
be. It's not like I'm going over a
。 这并不是说
volume of homes where I'm seeing the
我看到很多家庭里，
father sit with the family and the mom
父亲和家人、母亲坐在一起
and they're doing dinner and they're
吃饭，他们
having [snorts] conversations and
有说有笑，
they're, you know, it's this happy
你知道，那是一个幸福的
household. I I I only had a couple of
家庭。 我只有几个这样的
examples like that. I remember when I
例子。 我记得我
went over one of my friends houses um
去游泳队一个朋友家玩的时候，
from the swim team and I remember he had
我记得他有自己的
his own room.
房间。   简直太
It was like crazy.
疯狂了。
You get to close the door and [__] like
你可以关上门，这样的事情都是
this is your space. Yeah. This is my
你的空间。 是的。 这是我的
room. I had a hallway. We ain't have no
房间。 我有一个走廊。 我们根本没
goddamn room. We had a hallway. My bed's
地方住。 我们当时有一条走廊。 我的床
in the hallway. Every You could always
在走廊里。 你总能
see me. This is where [laughter]
看到我。 这就是我所在的地方[笑声]
this is where I am. Me and my brother
这就是我所在的地方。 我和我弟弟就在
right here in the hall on these bunk
走廊里的这些双层
beds. My friend had grass. He had a
床上。 我朋友家种了草坪。 他家有个
backyard. This is [__] crazy. Yeah,
后院。 这简直太疯狂了。 是啊，
we don't have none of this where we
我们住的地方根本没有这些
live. So, because that is the norm, I
。 因为那是常态，所以我
never it never affected me, right? Like
从来没受到影响，对吧？ 就像
I never
我从未经历过的那样，
I was never taken back by the obstacles
我从未被
of our household. My mom and dad just
我们家庭中的种种困难所吓倒。 我父母关系
didn't get along and it didn't work. All
不好，所以没能成功。
right. It is what it is.
好的。 就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Did you have male role models at the
你当时有男性榜样吗
time?
？
&gt;&gt; I don't think that I was in the space of
我不认为我当时对
when it comes to role model like at this
榜样有“不”的概念，
time like I I I didn't have the mindset
就像我当时并没有意识到
of what a role model is or should be. I
榜样是什么或者应该是什么样的。 我
just had good people around me who acted
身边都是些好人，他们就像我的
as like parenting aids to my mother to
育儿助手一样，帮助我妈妈应对
help her because of her schedule. But I
她繁忙的日程安排。 但我
never remember at that age looking at
从没记得在那个年纪的时候，我会看着
other families like, "Oh, this is what I
其他家庭说：“哦，这就是
this is what I want and this is what I'm
我想要的，这就是我
striving
努力想要
to get or gain." You know, like I it was
得到的东西。” 你知道，就像我当时那样，
it was shoulder shrug. A lot of shoulder
耸耸肩。 很多人
shrugs. It wasn't until I got older that
耸了耸肩。 直到我长大后，我才
laying down started to click in
开始以
differently. I mean, one of those
不同的方式理解我妈妈教给我的那些道理——或者说，我并不认为自己明白那些道理。 我的意思是，
lessons that your mother was trying to
你母亲试图灌输给你的那些道理，
&gt;&gt; in a Bible thousand%.
在圣经里都能找到。
&gt;&gt; With this, there's a
对此，我表示
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
赞同。
&gt;&gt; Best story ever. Best story um that I'm
史上最佳故事。 这是我
able to tell.
所能讲述的最好的故事。
&gt;&gt; She put something in the Bible that's
她把一些东西放进了圣经里，
hanging out there as you can see.
就像你看到的那样，就挂在那里。
&gt;&gt; Checks, man. I couldn't pay my rent. I
支票，伙计。 我交不起房租。 我
cannot pay my rent. I needed help. And
交不起房租了。 我需要帮助。
she was like, "Well, I'm not helping you
她当时说：“除非你开始读圣经，否则我是不会帮你的
until you start reading the Bible." And
。”
I was like, "Mom, I'm reading the
我当时就说：“妈妈，我在
Bible." I was lying. Just lying. I'm
读圣经。” 我撒谎了。 撒谎。 我正在
reading it. Come on, Mom. This is real.
读。 拜托，妈妈。 这是真的。
Mom, they're going to kick me out. Are
妈妈，他们要把我赶出去。
you reading your Bible? Yes.
你在读圣经吗？ 是的。
When you read your Bible, then talk to
当你读完圣经后，再来跟
me. And she did this for like a while.
我说话。 她这样做了大概一段时间。   有
And one day I was like, you know what,
一天我突然想到，你知道吗，
man? I was I was by myself and I was
伙计？ 我当时独自一人，
like, what am I going to do? I said, let
心想，我该怎么办？ 我说，让
me get this Bible.
我拿这本圣经来。
I read the Bible. And I opened up the
我读过圣经。 我打开圣经，结果发现里面竟然
checks had fell out. And I was like, you
散落着我的支票、房租，还有好几个月的房租支票。 我当时就想，你
know what?
知道吗？   真是
It's pretty amazing. [clears throat]
太神奇了。  [清嗓子]
Pretty amazing. And then I had to
真了不起。 然后我不得不
actually open a Bible and and start
打开圣经，开始
reading the Bible. But that was her way
阅读圣经。 但那当然是她
of of course knowing that I'm lying
知道我
first of all and b giving me like one of
首先在撒谎的方式，其次是给了我
the best lessons ever. You know
有史以来最好的一课。 你知道，不知从何时起，
she dropped started to click
她放弃了那些健身房，开始意识到
the idea of not starting things that I'm
不应该开始做自己
not going to finish.
无法完成的事情。
That's what really resonated with me the
这一点最让我感触颇深
most. So, like I started a lot of stuff
。 所以，就像我年轻时开始了很多事情，
that I didn't complete in the younger
但都没有完成
years. That was me and my mom's battle.
。 那是我和我妈妈之间的一场战斗。
No, you're gonna finish it. And she
不，你得把它完成。 她
would make me finish it. No, I want to
会逼我把它写完。 不，我想
quit. No, you're going to finish it. So,
辞职。 不，你得把它完成。 所以，
I ended up doing a lot of things with an
我最后做了很多事都带着一种
attitude, which is why I have to ask it.
态度，这也是我不得不问这个问题的原因。
&gt;&gt; Then, as I got older, you realize, well,
然后，随着年龄的增长，你会意识到，
why are you putting time into something
为什么要
in the beginning that you don't want to
在一开始就把时间投入到你不想
see through? Why? or just because you
坚持到底的事情上呢？ 为什么？ 或者仅仅因为你
have like a rough moment or a rough
遇到了一些困难时期或
patch, why is it so easy for you to
挫折，为什么你就这么容易
quit? Why why is the idea of quit so
放弃？ 为什么
quick to you to come up with and why are
你这么快就想到了放弃，而且
you so comfortable with the results of
对放弃的结果也如此坦然
that?
？
I shouldn't be
我不应该这样，
and that shouldn't be my like motto.
这不应该成为我的座右铭。
So, we don't stop. If we start
所以，我们不会停止。 如果我们开始做
something, we see it the entire way
某件事，我们就会坚持到底
through. And at the end of it, even if
。 最后，即使
you don't like it to the highest level,
你不是非常满意，
you know that you put your time, energy
你也知道你投入了时间和精力
into something that you're at least
去做一些至少让你感到
proud.
自豪的事情。   为
Proud that you did, proud that you were
你感到骄傲，为你
able to put a period on that sentence
能够为这件事画上句号而感到骄傲，
and now you can start the next thing.
现在你可以开始下一件事了。
But it's not until you complete
但只有当你完成
something that you can honestly sit with
某件事之后，你才能真正地坐下
yourself and go,
来，对自己说，这就是
what life is.
生活。
That's called seeing things through the
这叫做把事情从头到尾看完
entire way.
。
&gt;&gt; What was it that changed in you? Like
你身上发生了什么变化？ 是
what happened that made you suddenly
什么让你突然
start to take opportunities more
开始更加
seriously?
认真地对待各种机会？
&gt;&gt; When you saw the opportunity, you [__]
当你看到机会时，你却
off. I remember the the the
溜之大吉。 我记得我犯过
my big dummy moment and I've had a lot
很多蠢事，
so I don't know how much time we have to
所以我不知道我们还要经历多少蠢事，
go down but I got a lot of dummy moments
但我犯过很多蠢事，
but my biggest dummy moment
但我犯过最大的蠢事是
we hookie school to go and have our
我们逃学去参加
senior day. We go to Great Adventure
毕业典礼。 我们去了
theme park on the east coast and there
东海岸的大冒险主题公园，玩累了，
and we're talking. like eating and
我们开始聊天。 比如吃饭、
hanging out and all my friends were
闲逛，我的朋友们都在
talking about the college that they were
谈论他们即将
going to go to and they had already been
就读的大学，而且他们都已经被
accepted. They had already had letters
录取了。 他们之前已经收到信件
and [__]
之类的东西了。
When did y'all do this?
你们是什么时候做的这件事？
When did everybody apply? When did
大家是什么时候申请的？
When did you guys take the SAT? I just I
你们都是什么时候考的SAT？ 我刚
took mine, but I rushed it because I
拿了我的，但我走得很快，因为我
wanted to get here. I wanted a hookie.
想赶到这里。 我想逃课。
Wait.
等待。
How do you guys know where you going
你们怎么知道要去哪里
already? I had no knowledge, no idea.
？ 我对此一无所知，毫无概念。
All my friends have went on to the next
我的朋友们都进入下一
stage.
阶段了。
They let me be the dummy by myself. And
他们让我一个人当傻瓜。 就在那时我突然意识到，
nobody cares about you more than you
没有人比你更
should care about yourself.
关心你自己。
And nobody
没有人
is giving you the road map to like the
会告诉你如何才能喜欢
winds. You have to go find that
上风。 你得自己去找找那条
information. You got to go discover it.
信息。 你得自己去发现它。
You got to you got to want to get it.
你必须自己想要得到它。
You got to want to do it. And with the
你必须真心想做这件事。 有了
right help, the right world of
正确的帮助和正确的
knowledge, it can better help position
知识体系，它就能更好地帮助
you. But ultimately, you have to want to
你定位。 但归根结底，你必须想做，
you got to want to do it. and me and
你必须想做。 我什么
just not wanting to do [__] kind of put
都不想做，这让
me in a really [__] up position early
我很早就陷入了非常糟糕的境地
on.
。   是
&gt;&gt; Was it finding the thing, your thing
不是找到了那件让你
that put some wind in your sales and
销售业绩突飞猛进、
made you more of a apparently sort of
让你看起来更有
motivated individual? Cuz at some point
动力的事情？ 因为总有一天
you go from being that Kevin to the
你会从那个凯文变成
Kevin that can't stop working.
那个停不下来的凯文。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Well, you Well, that was my light
。 嗯，你……嗯，那是我灵光
bulb moment.
一闪的时刻。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; My light bulb moment was look at what
我恍然大悟的那一刻是：看看我
not applying myself got me. I feel like
不努力工作都得到了什么。 我觉得自己像个
the dummy that doesn't know what he
傻瓜，不知道自己的
wants to do with his life. And now I'm
人生方向。 我现在
at community college. I'm working as a
在社区大学就读。 我是一名
lifeguard. I eventually went to go work
救生员。 我最终去
for City Sports, which is a sneaker
City Sports工作了，那是一家运动
store. And I remember when I started
鞋店。 我还记得我开始
working at the sneaker store. Talked
在球鞋店工作的时候。
about this for years, too. I was like,
这个问题我们也讨论了很多年。 我当时想，
"Oh man, this is this is cool. This is
“哇，这太酷了。这就是
what I want to do. I got the thing that
我想做的。我终于做成
I want to do." I was so excited that I
我想做的事了。” 我当时非常兴奋，就
went and got a job, found a job. I'll do
去找了份工作。 我会一直做下去，
this forever and I'm going to make it to
我要达到
the highest level so I can have a
最高水平，这样我才能拥有自己的
career. So I become the manager and
事业。 所以我当上了经理，当了
after being the manager I work for
经理之后，我为
corporate and this is something that I
公司工作，这是我
can build like I was already inspiring
可以打造的东西，就像我已经很鼓舞人心了一样，
because I was like I I got to
因为我当时想，我得
[clears throat] figure out what I'm
[清嗓子]弄清楚我
doing with the rest of my life. What is
余生要做什么。
my life now? I'm panicking. What?
我现在的生活是什么样的？ 我慌了。 什么？
And I was flourishing
我当时
in the space of sneaker sales,
在运动鞋销售领域发展得非常顺利，
right? Education and college degree I
对吧？ 我没有学历和大学学位
don't have. But in the space of
。 但在
personality and sale,
个性和销售方面，
I was able to maneuver. This is it. This
我还是能够游刃有余的。 就是这样。 这
is my calling.
是我的使命。   正是在那时，
through ideas of my friends. You should
我朋友们的想法给了我真正的启发。 你应该
do standup because you're funny.
去做脱口秀演员，因为你很幽默。
You should try standup.
你应该试试单口喜剧。
&gt;&gt; Do you remember where you were when they
你还记得他们说那句话时你在哪里吗
said that?
？
&gt;&gt; In my workplace. I'm working every Hey,
在我的工作场所。 我每天都在工作。嘿，
I'm on the floor
我在车间，
&gt;&gt; and someone a colleague of yours that
你的同事
&gt;&gt; Alice colleague of mine that I work
爱丽丝和我一起工作
with.
。
&gt;&gt; What did your brain think when she said
她说这话的时候，你脑子里在想什么
that? Was it was it just blowing on a
？ 是它给原本就存在的火势吹上了
fire that was kind of already there or
火，还是
was it lighting the fire?
它点燃了火？
&gt;&gt; No, I think it the the fire was lit.
不，我认为是有人点燃了火。
Like I I never thought about pursuing
就像我一样，在这个想法出现之前，我从未想过要从事
standup comedy prior to like the idea
单口喜剧
came up. I was always funny, but I
。 我一直都很幽默，但我从来
wasn't like man I got to figure out how
没有想过要
to become a comedian. That was never a
成为一名喜剧演员。 我从来没想过这个问题
thought. I knew that I was very funny. I
。 我知道我很幽默。 我
knew that I was entertaining. I knew
知道我逗乐了大家。 我知道
that I can make people laugh. I love
我能逗人笑。 我喜欢
being the center of attention. I love
成为众人瞩目的焦点。 我喜欢
the idea of a stage and a light, but
舞台和灯光的想法，但这
that wasn't the thing. I wasn't like, I
并不是重点。 我当时并没有想，我已经明白了，接下来它会
got it and this is what it's going to
怎么
do. It was presented and then I went and
做。 它被介绍之后，我去参加了
did the amate and that's when I fell in
阿马特舞，就在那时我
love.
爱上了它。
&gt;&gt; Why did you like the stage and the light
你为什么喜欢舞台和灯光？
and and why did you like performing
你为什么喜欢表演
&gt;&gt; the laugh?
笑声？
&gt;&gt; Why? There's nothing better than to
为什么？ 没有什么比
laugh.
笑更美好的了。
There's nothing better than
没有什么比
being on stage having the bright light.
站在舞台上，沐浴在耀眼的灯光下更棒的了。
And
而
the only energy of good that you're able
你从所做的事情中唯一能带走的积极能量
to take away from what you're doing is
就是
the laugh. Ha.
笑声。 哈。
Hearing people laugh, I was like, "Oh
听到人们的笑声，我心想：“
[__]
糟了，
that feels different."
感觉不一样了。”
&gt;&gt; Why?
为什么？
&gt;&gt; This This is
这真是令人
This is energizing. This is like
精神振奋。 这就像问：
&gt;&gt; How does it make you feel about you?
你对自己有什么感觉？
&gt;&gt; I feel like I'm doing a service of good.
我觉得自己在做一件好事。
If I can make people feel better, if I
如果我能让人们感觉更好，如果我
can brighten up your day,
能让你的生活更美好，
it's a service of good.
那就是一件好事。
That means I'm like a shepherd of some
这意味着我有点像个牧羊人
sort. I'm
。 我的
I am responsible for making people feel
职责是让人们感觉
better. Oh my god. That means
更好。 我的天啊。 这意味着，
in success I can bring people to one
成功之后，我可以把人们带到同一个
destination
目的地，
and everybody can share a moment and a
让每个人都能分享一段时光和
laugh and all relate that it came from
欢笑，并且所有人都能感受到这一切都源于
me. Oh my god, this can get global. This
我。 我的天哪，这可能会蔓延到全球。 这
can get bigger. Well, this is starting
可能会变得更糟。 嗯，这种情况
to change now.
现在开始有所改变了。
Oh wow. Wait, this has opened up doors
哇哦。 等等，这
for me to do this or that or this or
为我做这件事、那件事或者其他事情打开了大门
that. It all started with the laugh. It
。 一切都始于那声笑声。
all started with the stage.
一切都始于舞台。
&gt;&gt; So, you went to that comedy show. Um,
所以，你去看了那场喜剧表演。 嗯，
I've got a I was looking at some of
我看了
those early clips of you performing.
你早期的一些表演片段。   真
It's funny cuz I think this is the early
搞笑，因为我觉得这是
2000s.
2000年代初期。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好的。
&gt;&gt; But, I mean, you probably
但是，我的意思是，你可能会说，
&gt;&gt; Oh my god. Caroline.
我的天哪。 卡罗琳。
Caroline. This right here. My best set
卡罗琳。 就是这个。 我
in the beginning of my career.
职业生涯初期发挥最好的一场比赛。
Everything I say here tonight is a joke,
我今晚说的都是玩笑，
okay? It is nothing else. I don't want
好吗？ 除此之外，别无其他。 我不想让
nobody take none of this stuff too
任何人把这些事看得太
serious.
认真。
&gt;&gt; I don't want nobody coming up to me
我不想演出结束后有人走过来对我
after the show saying, "Who's the funny
说：“现在谁才是搞笑的
one now?" Yeah. Yeah. This this that
人？” 是的。 是的。 这个这个那个
tape. So that was when you know
磁带。 所以，你知道，那时候
the thing I needed was a tape. Mhm.
我需要的是一盘磁带。 嗯。
&gt;&gt; And [clears throat] the reason why I
[清嗓子] 我
needed the tape was so that I could send
需要这段录像带的原因是为了把
it to the other comedy club so that they
它寄给另一家喜剧俱乐部，让他们看看
could have an example of me, my talent,
我的才华，
and then dictator judge if I can get a
然后由他们来评判我是否能获得
live audition in person.
现场试镜的机会。
&gt;&gt; And how old are you at that point?
那时你多大了？
&gt;&gt; Oh my god. Right there. I'm like
我的天啊。 就在那儿。 我才
18, 19.
18、19岁。太
&gt;&gt; That's crazy.
不可思议了。
&gt;&gt; 18, 19 years old.
18、19岁。
&gt;&gt; Cuz you're so That clip is so funny. I
因为你太……那段视频太搞笑了。 我
watched it this morning and like I was
今天早上看了，感觉自己
dying.
快要死了。
If you could understand the feeling of
如果你能体会到
getting off that stage, having a good
那种走下舞台，完成一场精彩
set and then them putting the tape in my
演出，然后他们把录像带放在我
hand, it was gold.
手里的感觉，那真是太棒了。
I got it. I got a good tape.
我得到了它。 我弄到了一盘不错的磁带。
I got to go make copies of my tape and I
我得去把磁带复制一份，然后
just got to send them to everybody. I
寄给所有人。 我以前只是
because it was it was it was valuable.
因为它有价值。
It was value. Started getting in comedy
它很有价值。 开始进喜剧
clubs, started getting auditions,
俱乐部，开始参加试镜，
started getting more
开始获得更多机会，
Oh my god. Kevin's up for an audition.
我的天哪。 凯文要去参加试镜。
Uh movie audition, cast of directors,
呃，电影试镜，导演们，
they all got that tape. Everybody got
他们都拿到了那盘录像带。 人人都有
that tape.
那盘录像带。
&gt;&gt; From that period onwards, from 18 to
从那段时期开始，也就是从 18 岁到
let's say to your early 20s, you were at
20 岁出头，你当时是
this point a very motivated individual.
一个非常有上进心的人。
You're working hard.
你很努力。
&gt;&gt; You're focused
你
&gt;&gt; very.
非常专注。
&gt;&gt; And what was your when you speak to your
那么，你
mom and your dad at this point about
在这个阶段和你的父母谈论
comedy? Do they think that's a serious
喜剧时，他们的想法是什么？ 他们认为这是一份正经
career?
职业吗？
&gt;&gt; My dad not as much cuz I didn't really
我跟爸爸联系不多，因为
talk to my dad through these years.
这些年我和爸爸几乎没怎么说话。
That's my dad was kind of dealing with
那是我爸爸在处理他
his his world of issues. Um, my mom, we
自己的一系列问题。 嗯，我和我妈之间
had an agreement. I had a certain amount
有个约定。 我当时只有一定的
of time to make comedy make sense and
时间来让喜剧变得有意义，并
figure out a way to support myself. Um,
找到养活自己的方法。 嗯，
if I didn't do it, then I had to go with
如果我不这么做，那我就只能听从
my mom's idea, which was education and
我妈妈的建议了，那就是一边接受教育
getting a job while getting my
一边找工作
education. My plan didn't it didn't
。 我的计划里并没有
involve college. I'm out. I'm done. I'm
提到上大学。 我走了。 我受够了。 我受够了
done. No more community. This is what I
。 社区不复存在。 这就是我
want to do. I got it. My I've never been
想做的。 我得到了它。 我从未像现在这样
more excited about my future. This is it
对自己的未来充满期待。
for me.
对我来说，这就是全部了。
How you going to make your money, Kevin?
凯文，你打算怎么赚钱？
I'm going figure it out. How you going
我会想办法的。 你打算怎么
to figure it out? I'mma figure it out
解决这个问题？ 我会想办法的
though. I'm just going to go down to the
。 我打算去
comedy clubs and I've been winning the
喜剧俱乐部表演，我在
amateur nights. I think the amateur
业余之夜的比赛中一直获胜。 我觉得业余
nights help me pay for my rent cuz I was
比赛能帮我支付房租，因为我经常在
winning the amateur nights. I won a
业余比赛中获胜。 我连续赢了
bunch of them in a row. In my mind, it
好几场。 在我看来，这
wasn't hard. It wasn't going to be hard
并不难。 这并不难，
because there was no other option. All
因为别无选择。 我把所有
my eggs were in this basket and I was
希望都寄托在这个选择上，我
very happy with that choice.
对这个选择非常满意。
I put every last egg in this thing.
我把最后一个鸡蛋都放进去了。
Nothing else matters but this. I promise
除了这件事以外，其他一切都不重要。 我保证
you I will figure it out.
我会想办法解决的。
&gt;&gt; Can you draw me a picture? If your
你能给我画幅画吗？ 如果你的
career was a graph?
职业生涯是一张图表呢？
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; Okay. So, I'm going to say here is 18
好的。 所以，我假设你当时18
years old and you're 40 46 now. So,
岁，而你现在40、46岁了。 所以，
you're 46 now. This is the axis of this
你现在46岁了。 这是这张图的横轴，
graph and on this axis we have let's say
这个横轴代表
success
成功，
and on this axis we have age. Can you
这个横轴代表年龄。 你能
draw me a p a line that shows how how
画一条线来表示
&gt;&gt; success and age? Okay. So success for me
成功和年龄之间的关系吗？ 好的。 对我而言，成功在于
knowing what I want to do in life comes
知道自己的人生目标
here.
。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. right now. Figuring out
。 现在。 想办法
money, revenue,
赚钱，获得收入，
just supporting yourself through telling
仅仅靠讲笑话来养活自己
a joke, man. Let's go. Let's go here for
，伙计。 我们走吧。 我们先到这里来一下
a second. We flatlining. Okay. Like, I'm
。 我们心跳停止了。 好的。 我是说，
I mean, I'm making people laugh.
我逗大家笑了。
I'm I'm getting in some comedy clubs,
我去了一些喜剧俱乐部演出，
but you only get paid with food. But
但是报酬只有食物。 但
then something weird happens where you
后来发生了一件奇怪的事，你
start figuring out, oh wait, here's kind
开始意识到，哦，等等，这就是
of where the spots come in. I can make
广告位的作用所在。我可以
money on the weekends and I can get 20
在周末赚钱，每个广告位能赚20
to $25 a spot. So rather than doing one
到25美元。 所以，与其只做一
spot, I would do, let's just say in a
处，不如说在一个
weekend, I got to the point where I was
周末做，我做到了要做
doing 25 to 28 sets.
25 到 28 组。
&gt;&gt; A weekend.
一个周末。
&gt;&gt; Wow. Well, I started making 500 $500 a
哇。 嗯，我开始每周赚500美元
week. $400 a week.
。 每周400美元。
&gt;&gt; How many years in is this to you making?
对你来说，这是几年时间里的作品？
&gt;&gt; 18. Let's say 22
18. 假设是 22
&gt;&gt; two. Yeah.
。 是的。
&gt;&gt; So, I was driving from Philadelphia to
所以，我当时每天都要从费城开车去
New York every day. But because of that,
纽约。 但正因为如此，
now you got to get into a comedy
你现在才需要去参加喜剧
festival. All right. So, now let's start
节。 好的。 好了，现在我们开始往
to go here because we did these spots
这里走，因为我们之前已经在这里待了
for a while. But then I got in a comedy
一段时间了。 但后来我参加了一个喜剧
festival. Oh [__] I got in a comedy
节。 妈的。 我入选了一个喜剧
festival.
节。
But that's when the industry saw me.
但正是在那时，业界注意到了我。
Who's this new guy? Who's this guy with
这个新来的小伙子是谁？ 这个
all this energy? Who's this [__] guy?
精力这么旺盛的人是谁？ 这他妈是谁？
This guy here, he's got something.
这家伙，他有两把刷子。
All right. So, I started meetings,
好的。 于是，我开始召开各种会议，
general meetings, and now I get a
全体会议，现在我得到了一个
holding deal. So, let's go up a little
控股协议。 那么，我们再往上走一点
bit. I think it was ABC. They gave me
。 我想应该是ABC电视台。 他们给了我
like 250 grand. So, they're holding you
大约25万美元。 所以，他们扣押你，
in hopes they get something. Nothing
希望从中得到些什么。 什么也没
happens. So, we're flatlining here. Now,
发生。 所以，我们这里已经陷入停滞状态了。 现在，
I'm just waiting for the phone to ring.
我正在等电话铃响。
That's how this works. What if I want to
事情就是这样运作的。 如果我想
create my own thing? Create a show. Oh
创作自己的作品呢？ 制作一档节目。
my god. Show gets picked up. I create
我的天啊。 节目被电视台选中。 我创作了
something else. They decide to do it. Oh
别的作品。 他们决定这么做。 糟了
[__] there's a pattern. I can do that
，这其中有规律。 我可以随心所欲地做
as much as I want. I can treat that just
。 我可以像处理
how I was treating the spots and stuff
我在纽约遇到的那些斑点之类的东西一样处理它
in New York. I'm out. I'm moving to LA.
。 我走了。 我要搬去洛杉矶。
No plan, no nothing. Flatline.
没有计划，什么都没有。 直线。
I'm here. I just did it. I just came and
我在这里。 我刚刚就这么做了。 我刚搬进来就离开了
moved out. [__] man. This is weird. I
。 操，老兄。 这很奇怪。 我
don't like this [laughter]
不喜欢这份工作[笑声]
work. I'm not getting no work, man. This
。 我没工作啊，兄弟。 这
[__] is is real stagnant. I'm going on
事儿真是停滞不前。 我要
the road. I want to I want to work the
上路了。 我想，我想在
road. I'm going to be a headliner. I'm
路上工作。 我将成为头条人物。 我
going to do colleges. So, I'm going to
要去上大学。 所以，我要
get college money and comedy club money
挣大学学费和喜剧俱乐部的演出费，
and I'm going to do it. I worked that
然后我就去做这件事。 我花了
for a very long time. Right. Very, very
很长时间研究这个问题。 正确的。 经过了很
long time to the point where now I'm
长时间，我现在已经能够场场爆满的
selling out comedy clubs. After I
喜剧俱乐部演出了。 在我
started selling out comedy clubs,
开始场场爆满的喜剧俱乐部演出之后，
my person at the time was like, "Yo, we
我当时的经纪人就说：“嘿，我们
can probably do theaters. You're adding
或许可以去剧院演出了。你现在演出场次越来越
a lot of shows.
多。
&gt;&gt; Are you a millionaire at this point?
你现在是百万富翁了吗？”
&gt;&gt; No. No. I'm just an active active comic.
不，不，我只是个活跃的喜剧演员。
The next stage of success, right, was
成功的下一个阶段，对吧，就是
let's go from comedy clubs to theaters.
从喜剧俱乐部进军剧院。
All right. Boom. Let's go here. Then
好，砰！我们去那里。然后
let's go up again. Theaters start
我们再往上走。剧院的票
selling out real quick. Oh, [__] Let's
很快就卖光了。哦，天哪。我们
go from theaters, right, to like arenas.
再从剧院进军体育馆之类的场地。
Oh [__] Will Packer, he was like, "I
哦，糟糕。威尔·帕克说：“我
got this book that I want to make a
有一本书，我想把它拍成
movie. It's called Think Like a Man.
电影。” 它叫做《像男人一样思考》。
Steve Harvey wrote it. I think you're
史蒂夫·哈维写的。 我觉得你真是太
funny as hell. I've been tracking you on
幽默了。 我一直在关注你的
tour. I want you to be the star." We
巡演。  “我想让你当主角。”我们
film it. Think Like a Man comes out.
拍了这部电影。《像男人一样思考》上映了。《
Think Like a Man did 90 something
像男人一样思考》
million dollars in the box office. And
票房收入超过9000万美元。
Will says, "Hey man, working with you is
威尔说：“嘿，伙计，和你一起工作
great. Let's do something else. I got
太棒了。” 我们做点别的吧。 我买了
this movie called Ride Along. You and
一部叫《佐州之旅》的电影。 你和
Ice Cube would be great." Boom. Ride
Ice Cube合作肯定很棒。” 砰！《佐州巡警》票房
Along does 140. Like the movies just
140。就像电影突然
started to pow, get hard, central
开始火起来一样，《硬汉》、《
intelligence, me and the rock. I mean,
中央情报局》、《我和巨石强森》。我的意思是，
it just happened so fast. So now because
这一切发生得太快了。现在
the movies are working, I'm like, this
电影很成功，我就觉得，这
is so cool. But while this is happening,
太酷了。但与此同时，
I should figure out like how to kind of
我应该想想如何
create my own source of like
创造属于自己的
opportunity. Like people keep bringing
机会来源。人们不断地给
opportunities to me. How do I create my
我带来机会。我该如何创造
own source of opportunity? I'm gonna
自己的机会来源呢？我要
start a a production company.
成立一家制片公司。
I need to start developing. But now I'm
我需要开始开发。但现在我
like, I created that. Let's create
想，我已经创造了这个。让我们创造
something else. So then I say, let's go
一些新的东西吧。所以我说，不如就成立
like Heartbeat Ventures and let's do a
Heartbeat Ventures，做一家
VC. Oh man, I'm creating a bunch of
风险投资公司。天哪，我正在创造很多
stuff. Hey, these entities around me,
东西。嘿，我周围的这些机构，
it's all happening because my likeness.
这一切都是因为我的影响力。
My likeness allows me to get in these
我的影响力让我能够进入这些
rooms and start relationships and put
圈子，建立人脉，让
myself in a position to make deals and
自己处于能够达成交易并
create long-term revenue. How do I get
创造长期收益的位置。我该如何获得
more of that? Wow.
更多这样的影响力呢？哇。
Like NASCAR, people attach themselves to
就像纳斯卡赛车一样，人们会把自己与
the car they think is doing the best.
…… 他们认为表现最好的车。
I'm a car. I should have brand
我就是一辆车。我应该和品牌
partnerships.
合作。比如
Chase, DraftKings, Fablettics.
Chase、DraftKings、Fablettics。
I should have my own brands and
我应该拥有自己的品牌和
businesses that I'm building where more
业务，打造属于自己的品牌，这样
opportunity for long-term revenue can
才能获得更多长期收入的机会
present itself.
。比如
Grand Cormino, wine, spirits. Now, oh
Grand Cormino 葡萄酒和烈酒。哇哦
wow, I've grabbed this concept of
，我抓住了“
business control ownership and mirrored
企业控制权和所有权”这个概念，并将
it with Kevin's drive and entertainment
其与 Kevin 的干劲、娱乐精神
and visibility.
和知名度结合起来。
Leverage that to get me into the rooms
利用这些优势，我可以进入一些
where I may not be as visible or as
我可能不太显眼或影响
strong, but once I'm embedded into these
力不足的场合，但一旦我融入其中
environments, I can bring them value. I
，就能为他们带来价值。我
can help amplify or uplift their brands,
可以帮助提升他们的品牌和
their products. So, my case study of
产品。所以，我的案例研究是
Fablettics,
Fablettics
of DraftKings, before I got there versus
和 DraftKings，在
after I got there, Chase financial
我加入前后，Chase 的金融
literacy, like C4, like these are things
知识普及项目，比如 C4，在这些项目中，
where I'm now, well, I'm not just a
我现在不仅仅是
partner, I'm an owner, I'm a endorser,
合作伙伴，我是所有者，我是代言人，
I'm an ambassador.
我是品牌大使。
Oh, wow. This
哇哦。这才是
is where the real money is made. The
真正赚钱的地方。 创造。
ecosystem of life. How do you how do you
生命的生态系统。你如何
put yourself in a position to be a part
让自己融入
of everyday movement in life?
日常生活的方方面面？
You're looking at things in a much
你要以更细致的视角看待事物
granular scale. And now I go way back
。现在，我回想起以前漫无
to when I was like not really focusing,
目的、
not thinking about life, not thinking
不思考生活、不思考
about how things connect. I'm now able
事物之间联系的日子。现在，我能够
to tap into the lessons that my mom
汲取母亲的教诲
gave. And I'm like,
。我意识到，
all good things that happen happen when
所有美好的事情都会在
they're supposed to. But now I'm poised
它们应该发生的时候发生。如今，我
and polished enough with a mindset that
足够沉稳成熟，拥有了清晰的心态，明白自己
understands, well, I don't want to start
不会轻易开始
something that I'm not going to finish.
无法完成的事情。
So, if I'm going to put myself in
所以，如果我要让自己处于
position to do these things, how do I
能够完成这些事情的位置，我该如何
make sure that my partners know I'm
确保我的合作伙伴知道我
willing to give my all?
愿意全力以赴？
How do I show that I'm not going to
我该如何展现我不会
quit?
放弃？
Which back here, my mom's biggest lesson
我母亲最重要的教诲
was, you're not quitting. If you start
就是：不要放弃。如果你开始做
it, you're going to finish it. So, how
某件事，你就会完成它。那么，
do I make my partners that I'm now
我该如何让我的合作伙伴
saying you should work with me? How do I
相信我应该与他们合作？我该如何……
make Netflix secure and knowing that
Netflix 很安全，而且你知道，
when you get me, you get 100% of me and
当你得到我的时候，你得到的是 100% 的我，
I'm never going to quit. I'm going to
我永远不会放弃。我会
finish it all. How do I make my other
完成所有的事情。我该如何让我的其他
studio affiliates understand and working
工作室合作伙伴理解，以及
with Heartbeat, it is in my best
与 Heartbeat 的合作，为
interest to bring you great product,
你们带来优质的产品和
great material so that you understand
素材符合我的最佳利益，这样你们才能了解
what we do so that we can continue to
我们所做的工作，从而我们能够继续
drive a business that has the best
推动一项
interest for both of us. How do I sell
对我们双方都有利的业务。我该如何说服
you on that? So now my business of sell
你们呢？所以现在我的销售业务
mirrors and matches my business of grow.
与我的增长业务相辅相成。
Nothing that I'm doing doesn't go hand
我所做的一切都是相辅相成的
in hand. And I should be able to embed
。我应该能够将我现在运营中涉及的
the products or the partnerships that
产品或合作关系
I'm now operationally like attached to
融入
into the ecosystem of entertainment. So
到娱乐生态系统中。例如，
if I have a C4 can and I'm doing an
如果我有一个 C4 罐头，我正在开展一个
activation and health and wellness, well
健康和保健方面的推广活动，那么
C4 is my partner, I should integrate you
C4 是我的合作伙伴，我应该让你们参与到
in this opportunity. Hey, my movie, we
这个机会中来。嘿，我的电影里，我们
have an opportunity to basically wear a
有机会穿戴一个
product. I should be in Fablettics in
产品。我应该在
this scene because this makes my partner
这个场景中穿着 Fablettics 的产品，因为这会让我的合作伙伴
feel valued and positioned. Oh wow. This
感到被重视和认可。哇哦。这
is what I do. I elevate
就是我所做的。
I I I basically navigate my space of
我基本上是以一种
ownership in a way like only I can to
只有我才能做到的方式来掌控我的领域，从而
elevate my partners so that my partners
提升我的合作伙伴，让他们
go and say you're different. This is
说：“你与众不同。这很
different and this is what we need more
特别，这正是我们需要的
of.
。”
That's my graph.
这就是我的发展轨迹。
&gt;&gt; I've got some questions about the graph.
我对这个轨迹有一些疑问。
So, I guess the parts that I'm curious
我想问的是，
you're 18 where like nothing's really
18岁那段初期，感觉一切都停滞不前，
&gt;&gt; because so many of my listeners,
因为我的很多听众，
probably most of them are in some
可能大部分人，都在
pursuit or sort of professional endeavor
追求某种事业或职业，但都处于一种
in their life in this kind of stagnant
停滞状态。
&gt;&gt; where maybe they enjoy it, but like it
他们或许很享受这份工作，但它
ain't paying the bills. No one believes
无法维持生计。没有人相信
in them. Maybe some of their friends are
他们。也许当
rolling their eyes when they tell them
他们告诉朋友们
what they're doing. When you look back
自己在做什么时，朋友们还会翻白眼。当你回首
on this season of life, like what is
这段人生阶段时，你会如何描述
through it?
它？你是如何度过的？
believed that I was funny when I said I
当我说我
was going to be a comedian. Like they
想成为一名喜剧演员时，没有人相信我幽默。他们
were like, "You funny but not comedian
会说：“你很幽默，但不是那种喜剧演员才会有的
funny."
幽默。”
Like my friends were,
我的朋友们会说：
"Yeah, what do you mean you gonna get on
“是啊，那你呢？” 你是说你要上台
stage? What do you mean I'm going to get
表演吗？ 你的意思是我要
on stage? I'm going be a comedian."
上台？  “我要当喜剧演员。”
G like how? Like Eddie Murphy. Like I'm
像什么？像艾迪·墨菲那样。就像我要当
going be a comedian. Yeah, but you're
喜剧演员一样。是啊，但你
never going to be Eddie Murphy. Yeah, I
永远也成不了艾迪·墨菲。是啊，我
know. But I'm I'm saying like I'm going
知道。但我的意思是，我要
to do it. Like I'm going to be I'm be a
去做。就像我要成为
star. No,
明星一样。不，
I don't know, man.
我不知道，伙计。我
I don't know about the whole star thing.
对明星这事儿不太了解。
I think you're tripping. I think I don't
我觉得你有点想太多了。我觉得，我觉得，我觉得不是
I don't I don't think that's it. Nobody
那样。没有人像
you're making for yourself like you do.
你一样对自己做的决定那么有信心。
So if you're waiting for that to connect
所以，如果你
in the beginning stages, it may or may
在初期就等着成功，那可能成功，也可能
not. If it doesn't, it shouldn't prevent
失败。如果没成功，也不应该阻止
you from like following through on
你继续走下去，去做
you.
你认为应该做的事。
The money is never coming fast.
钱从来不会来得很快。
We're in a time today where this
我们生活在一个时代，这
generation has found ways to make money
一代人找到了
that we've never seen before. like the
前所未有的创业赚钱方式。比如
the social media machine and how this
社交媒体，以及这
generation navigates that machine to
一代人如何驾驭这个机器。
find revenue and to own
找到收入来源并拥有自己的事业简直
is unbelievable. That didn't exist. We
难以置信。以前根本没有这种机会。
didn't have the like in in my time. We
在我那个年代，根本没有这种模式。我们
didn't have that.
没有那种机会。
&gt;&gt; We just had the struggle
我们只有挣扎，
&gt;&gt; and the struggle left you with days of
而挣扎会让你整天
like literally sitting in the living
坐在
room going, "What the [__] man?"
客厅里，心里想着：“这他妈到底是怎么回事？”
&gt;&gt; So, why didn't you quit? because no
所以，你为什么不放弃？因为
money, everyone's doubting it. What What
没钱，每个人都在质疑你。
were you believing in?
你当时相信什么？
&gt;&gt; I was believing in the idea that I
我相信我
finally found the thing that I want to
终于找到了自己想做的事
do.
。
&gt;&gt; So, it was passion that was really you
所以，真正支撑你的是激情。
&gt;&gt; I I found the thing that I want to do
我找到了自己想做的事，
and I'm not going to quit it because I
我不会放弃，因为我
love it this much and I strongly believe
太爱它了，我坚信
that the sun is at the end of this dark
黑暗隧道的尽头就是阳光
tunnel, but I got to be willing to get
，但我必须做好到达
there. And I I just don't know how to
那里的准备。我只是还不知道该怎么去
get there yet, but I'mma figure it out.
，但我会找到办法的。我
Guess I'm going to LA.
想我要去洛杉矶了。
I was in New York, but after New York,
我之前在纽约，但离开纽约之后，
they say go to LA. I'm gone.
他们都说要去洛杉矶。我走了。
What you going to do when you get there?
你到了那里打算做什么？
I'll figure it out.
我会 想办法解决。
I can always get on the plane and fly
我随时可以坐飞机去任何
where I got to go for stand up. If
我想去的地方表演脱口秀。如果真是那样
that's the case, I can always go and
，我当然可以去靠
make money doing standup
脱口秀赚钱，
if I have to, but I'm not going to get
但如果非得那样，我不可能成为
to the star
明星
by just doing that. I got to I got to go
。我必须亲自去
there. I got to get close to it. I got
那里。我必须接近它。我必须去感受它。我必须去
to smell it. I got to feel it. I got to
体验它。我必须
find out where the people are that are
找到那些也在
trying to do it, too. I got to get
努力的人。我必须去上
acting classes. I got to I got to get
表演课。我必须去好莱坞转转
around the the the Hollywood. Like, what
。比如，好莱坞到底
is H? I got to get there. And what
是什么？我必须去那里。
happens when you're there? It fuels
当你到了那里会发生什么？它会激发
another another like
另一种
another appetite of of hunger cuz I'm
欲望，就像另一种饥渴，因为我身处
there in real time. I'm seeing people
其中。我能更清楚地看到人们
better. I remember I tell this Cat
。我记得我讲过一个关于凯特·
Williams story and I don't I don't even
威廉姆斯的故事，但我甚至不确定我是否跟
think I told Cat this. Uh
凯特说过这件事。嗯，
there was a moment where I was opening
有一次我为
for Cat Williams and
凯特·威廉姆斯做开场嘉宾，
I remember
我记得当时我在
I remember being at the the BET Comedy
BET喜剧
Awards
奖颁奖典礼上，
and I'm in I'm in attendance and this is
我出席了，
like you know I'd had a couple of shots
你知道的。 我之前也尝试过
at some things but they just you know it
一些事情，但你知道，就是不行，就是没成功。那些
the the the pilots I thought were going
我以为会火的试播集也没火，那些
things that I thought were going to
我以为会
happen, they just weren't. It just
发生的事也没发生。感觉就是
didn't seem like it was adding up,
不对劲，
right? Like the the roles are little
对吧？那些角色都是
small roles or little small cameos, but
些小角色或者客串，但就是
like it wasn't it wasn't the thing. And
不对劲。
I remember Cat Williams set during the
我记得卡特·威廉姆斯在
BET Comedy Awards, he had like a leopard
BET喜剧奖颁奖典礼上的表演，他穿着一身豹纹
suit,
西装，
destroyed,
彻底引爆了全场，彻底
destroyed the Comedy Awards, destroyed
引爆了
this moment. And
那个时刻。
audience goes crazy, stands up.
观众都疯了，站了起来。
I remember being in the audience and I
我记得当时我就在观众席上，
was like, that's it.
心想，就是它了。
I say like that's the that's the thing.
我说，就是它了，就是它了。就是那种
that thing, that reaction, that roar,
反应，那种欢呼，
that moment.
那种时刻。
I got to be patient because my moment is
我必须耐心等待，因为我的时刻终会
going to come. I witnessed his moment.
到来。我见证了他的时刻。在
And he after that moment,
那之后
it was Friday after next, you know, that
，你知道，就是下下个星期五，
I mean, he went on and started to do
他继续前进，开始
crazy things in his career, right? But I
在他的事业上做一些疯狂的事情，对吧？ 我
witnessed the moment. And in that
亲眼见证了那一刻。那
moment, my takeaway was that he was
一刻，我的感受是他已经为
ready for the moment.
那一刻做好了准备。
his material, the the jokes, everything,
他的段子、笑话，一切都完美无瑕
it all hit. And I didn't watch it in a
。我当时看的时候并没有
in a manner of like jealous or angry. I
嫉妒或生气，而是觉得，就这样了
was like that that's it. Like he's
。他
probably out of here after this. I mean,
可能就此告别舞台了。毕竟，
it's the BT Comedy Awards. At the time,
这是BT喜剧奖。当时
I'm like, this is the biggest thing
我就想，这可是史上最盛大的活动
ever, right? This the comedy awards. By
，对吧？这是喜剧奖啊！
the way, they never did the Comedy
顺便说一句，他们之后再也没办过喜剧
Awards again. I think this is like the
奖了。我想这应该是
last one they did. But that moment,
他们最后一次举办了。但是，
if the ball is dropped in that moment,
如果那一刻出了差错，
then the moment goes. You don't know
那么机会就溜走了。你不知道
when the moment is presenting itself,
机会何时到来，
but I'm staying with the thing because I
但我会坚持下去，因为我
know that the moment is going to come.
知道机会总会到来。
And when I'm in the moment, if I knock
当我真正抓住机会，如果我能完美演绎
that [__] moment out the park,
，
all things will change. But you may not
一切都会改变。但你可能不
know it. You may not know when the
知道。你可能不知道
moment comes.
机会何时到来。
&gt;&gt; When did your moment come?
你的机会是什么时候到来的？
&gt;&gt; Shaq's all-star comedy jam. The reason
沙奎尔·奥尼尔的全明星喜剧表演。
why I equated with the story with cat.
我之所以把这件事和Cat的故事联系起来，是因为……
Uh I believe it was Tommy Davidson. It
呃，我记得是Tommy Davidson主持的。那
was D set of the Entertainer was a host.
是《D Set of the Entertainer》的演出，我是压轴嘉宾
I headlined it. I end up having one of
。结果我奉献了
the best sets that I've ever had. And at
我有史以来最棒的演出之一。在
the end of the Shacks Allstar Comedy
Shacks Allstar Comedy
Jam, I say good night and they do like a
Jam的最后，我说了声晚安，然后他们做了个
slow motion walkoff.
慢动作退场。
It's a slow motion thing and it's like
就是那种慢动作，我走着走着
I'm I'm walking, the crowd stands up and
，观众们都站起来，
they're going crazy. By the way, I don't
疯狂欢呼。顺便说一句，我不
know the slow motion walkoff is going to
知道
happen in the edit of the special, but I
特辑剪辑版里会不会保留这个慢动作退场，但我
remember in real time crowds standing
记得当时观众都站
up, stars were there. Everybody was
起来了，明星们也都在。所有人都
there, right? And in that moment,
到场了，对吧？那一刻，
show you how [__] crazy the world is.
你就能感受到这个世界有多么疯狂。
This is why I hate that like me and Cat
这就是为什么我讨厌……我和Cat
went through our stuff and we're much
经历了一些事情，
better now. I'm going show you how the
现在我们和好多了。我要告诉你，
world aligns.
世界是如何运转的。Cat当时就
Cat was in the audience. The Shacks
在观众席上。Shacks
Allstar Comedy Jam and Cat was watching
Allstar Comedy Jam，Cat在看
the show. He was just there as a fan,
演出。他只是个粉丝，
but at this time everything big is
但就在那一刻…… 一切都在
happening.
发生，而且都是大事。
And I had a moment
我经历了一个瞬间，
and that was the moment that then took
那一刻就像
me and shot me out the cannon.
炮弹一样把我发射了出去。
And if I wasn't prepared for the moment
如果我没有为那一刻做好准备，如果
and I wouldn't have known all the things
我没有预料到
to come. Okay. But that then set up I
接下来发生的一切，那肯定不会发生。好吧。但那之后，我
was releasing my special. My special
发行了我的脱口秀特辑。我的特辑叫《
seriously funny. I was taping in two
Seriously Funny》。两周后我就要录制了
weeks.
。
So Shaq's Allstar Comedy Jam goes they
然后，沙奎尔·奥尼尔的全明星喜剧秀播出，他们
rush to put it out. It crushes. I then
赶紧把特辑也放了上去。结果大获成功。之后我
tape my comedy special. Seriously funny
录制了我的喜剧特辑。《Seriously Funny》
was my next special. Seriously funny
是我的下一个特辑。《Seriously Funny》也大获
destroys,
成功，
but it only destroyed because of Shaq's
但它的成功完全是因为沙奎尔·奥尼尔的
All-Star Comedy Jam. And the audience
全明星喜剧秀。当时的观众都
that watched that and I was like, "Oh my
看了那场演出，我心想：“我的
god, this guy showed up in droves for
天哪，这家伙为了《
Seriously Funny." And then Seriously
Seriously Funny》来了这么多人。”然后《Seriously
Funny was like, "Oh [__] this big ass
Funny》的制作方也意识到：“我的天，这个
special." And then the arenas and
特辑太火了。”之后，体育馆演出等等，
everything. Boom, boom, boom, boom,
一切都火爆起来。砰砰砰砰砰
boom.
。
&gt;&gt; So about 12, 13 years from the moment
所以，从
you did your first sort of standup event
你第一次参加脱口秀活动
to you having your moment. And I find
到你迎来自己的高光时刻，大概过了12、13年。我觉得
that fascinating cuz those 13 years most
这很神奇，因为这13年里，大多数
people
人……
&gt;&gt; aren't willing to do something for 13
没人愿意苦练13
years without their moment showing up.
年却看不到属于自己的时刻。
&gt;&gt; Like when you hear like I don't know
就像你
[__] on Instagram or quotes or you watch
在Instagram上看到一些励志语录，或者看一些
motivational videos and stuff.
励志视频之类的东西时，会觉得“我什么都不懂”。
&gt;&gt; If they told you that it would take 13
如果有人告诉你，
years for you to have your moment,
你需要13年才能迎来属于你的时刻，
almost nobody would take part.
几乎没人会参与。真的没
&gt;&gt; Nobody. No. and those 13 years of your
人。绝对不会。而这13年的
training.
训练，你却要付出那么多。就像
&gt;&gt; I mean, so Scooter Braun told me one
Scooter Braun曾经跟我说过
time, he was like, what makes him
，他与众不同的地方在于
different is the work that he's willing
他愿意为之
to do in something. And he was like, you
付出的努力。他说，
know, if they were giving out like a
如果
million dollars for somebody that can
有人能
hit a fast ball pitch, you know, from a
击中
from the best pitcher in baseball,
棒球界最优秀投手投出的快速球，奖金高达一百万美元，
right? And this thing will basically
那么这项挑战基本上
require everybody everybody's going to
需要所有人参与，每个人都会
go and try to hit this because everybody
去尝试，因为每个人都
wants the million dollars. So the first
想要那一百万美元。所以，
day of the announcement, the line to hit
在宣布这项挑战的第一天，
this pitch is going to be
排队的人肯定会
droves, right? Like I mean millions of
络绎不绝，对吧？我的意思是，会有成千上万的
people, who knows how many people would
人，谁知道会有多少人
be in this line and people would go up
排队，然后有人上去被
and strike out and after that they would
三振出局，之后他们会
go, "Damn, it's over." like I missed.
说：“天哪，  “结束了。”就像我错过了机会一样。
Not many people would like miss and then
没多少人会喜欢错过机会，然后又重新
go stand back in line to go hit the ball
排队去击球
again. He was like, I'm going to keep
。他却说，我会一直
getting in line. What you'll find is
排队。你会发现，
that the line will get smaller and
队伍会越来越短，
because of how many people are dropping
因为越来越多的人
out and optioning not to wait and do the
放弃，选择不再等待，不再经历那段
hard thing again.
艰难的历程。
That comparison and that
这种比喻和
world of understanding is like something
理解
very well, right? Not many people are
很贴切地形容了人生，对吧？没多少人愿意
going to wait through the 13 years of
忍受13年
like [__] hardship. Most people opt
这种狗屁的苦难。大多数人会
out at year two,
在第二年，
maybe three, no money, whatever. I need
或许第三年就放弃，没钱了，等等。我
to figure something else out. Year six,
得另谋出路。到了第六年，
[__] this man. Stupid. What am I doing?
去他妈的。蠢死了。我在干什么？我
Why am I doing it? Right? I'm going to
为什么要这么做？对吧？我要
go find the quick avenue or the quick
去找捷径，或者快速
return because money is the that's what
回报，因为对
it boils down to for most people.
大多数人来说，最终都是为了钱。
Where's the money? Where am I making the
钱在哪儿？我怎么
money?
赚钱？
When the money comes, it comes.
钱来了自然就来了。
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
What you find is that it's not hard to
你会发现，
make money once you start making money.
一旦你开始赚钱，赚钱就不难了。 金钱。
You learn
你会学会
how to make money. like you. It comes
如何赚钱。就像你一样。它
with education. It comes with
来自教育。它来自
understanding and it comes with a better
理解，也来自更强大的
resource of mind that makes you go, "No,
思维能力，让你能够说：“不，
I'm going to do this and I'm going to
我要去做这件事，我要
build this and I'm going to go here. I'm
建立这个，我要去那里。” 我要
going to meet. I'm going to present. I
去见。 我将进行演讲。 我
have an idea. I'm going to pitch it."
有个主意。 我要去推销它。”
like you you're now a a much better
就像你现在更像一台
machine because you understand
机器，因为你明白了
money is no longer the thing that you
金钱不再是你最初
think it was when you get to it. But
想象的那样。但
getting to it to get that understanding,
为了获得这种理解，
you lose the pack.
你却失去了同伴。
You lose the pack because the pack is
你失去了同伴，因为他们会想：“
like, I want it here. And because it
我想要它在这里。”但因为它
didn't show up here, I got to go figure
没有出现，我不得不另辟蹊径，找到
out a new thing to do that's going to
新的方法来实现它
give it to me here. And they got to
。他们
recycle like
就像在循环往复，
&gt;&gt; they lose focus.
失去了焦点。
&gt;&gt; Yes. You you're never completing
是的，你永远无法完成
anything. You never finish nothing. So
任何事情。你永远无法完成任何事情。所以，
the thing that you think you're focusing
你以为自己专注于某件事，却
on, you keep quitting to start something
不断放弃，转而去做你
else that you think is an idea and it's
认为是另一个想法的事情，这
just a cycle. It's a cycle.
只是一个循环。这是一个循环。
&gt;&gt; Don't you notice that people come up to
你难道没有注意到，人们会来找我吗？我
I notice this a lot with young
经常在年轻的创业者身上看到这种情况，
entrepreneurs, especially those that
尤其是那些
aren't having success. They start one
不成功的人。他们开始做一
thing. Well, they when they come and
件事。当他们来
tell you what they do, they tell you 17
告诉你他们在做什么时，他们会告诉你17
things.
件事。17件。
&gt;&gt; None of them have ever say 17 things.
他们中没有人真正说过17件事。
&gt;&gt; Mhm. And they think that more doing more
嗯。他们认为做更多的事情。
things is increasing the probability of
事情越多，成功的概率就越高
success.
。100
&gt;&gt; 100% where it's the opposite. [laughter]
% 的情况下恰恰相反。[笑声]
&gt;&gt; It's the opposite. It's the it's the
恰恰相反。关键在于，你要做的是
thing that you actually thought of that
你真正思考过的事情，
you are going to put 100% of your mind
你要投入百分之百的精力
and focus into to complete. And then
和注意力去完成它。之后
after that, you're able to pick it apart
，你才能把它拆解开来，
and take the good, the bad, the whatever
吸取好的、坏的、任何经验，然后要么重新开始
improve it or make a decision to do
改进，要么决定去做
something else. But you finished. I made
别的事情。但你已经完成了。我选择了单
the choice that standup comedy was what
口喜剧作为
I was going to finish. I made a choice
我要完成的事情。我选择
that becoming a good comic and a good
成为一名优秀的喜剧演员和优秀的
headliner, if I focused and did it well,
领衔主演，如果我专注于此并做得出色，
that would open up the doors for me to
这将为我打开通往
do everything else that I want to do. If
其他所有我想做的事情的大门。如果
I don't have that,
我没有做到这一点，
how do I expect to get in?
我怎么指望能进入这个领域呢？
&gt;&gt; I was speaking to Evan at Snapchat and
我和 Snapchat 的 Evan 聊过，
he was talking about T-shaped people. So
他谈到了 T 型人才。这种人对
of a lot of things, but then you're like
很多事物都有广泛的了解，但同时又
really deep on one particular thing. And
在某一方面非常精通。而你
guess you could see as like screw that
所说的这方面几乎可以看作是…… 就像，这
gets you into the industries. So for me,
能让你进入各个行业一样。对我来说，
mine would have originally been
我最初的专业是
marketing, but I was able to use that
市场营销，但我能够利用这种
like deep expertise to then launch this
深厚的专业知识创办这家
media business cuz it's still the same
媒体公司，因为这仍然是
game of marketing that I did for for 15
我从事了15
years. I was able to go into like the
年的市场营销工作。我能够进入
stock market because they really needed
股市，因为他们确实需要
to understand marketing. And it was that
了解市场营销。正是这种对
deep expertise in one thing that was my
某一领域的深厚专业知识，让我
leverage in all of these really
在所有这些
interesting rooms. It's kind of what you
重要的场合都拥有了优势。这有点
were saying at the start like you had
像你一开始说的，你拥有
this deep expertise, this deep IP
深厚的专业知识和丰富的知识产权
experience value that allowed you to
经验，这让你能够以
like break in as an investor and then to
投资者的身份进入市场，然后进入
production and all these other areas. I
制作和其他所有领域。我的
mean the value the value for me it was
意思是，对我来说，价值在于
self but
自我，在于
the value of self and understanding
理解
of how to truly control and operate that
如何真正控制和运营它，
and navigate that correctly.
并正确地驾驭它。
That's a that's a world of its own. So
这本身就是一个独立的世界。所以，
the bigger that the star gets,
明星越耀眼，
the brighter that the star shines.
光芒就越强烈。
If you are paying attention, it's only
如果你足够用心，它只
positioning you to go in places where
会让你进入那些
people say, "Oh my god, I know you." And
人们会说“天哪，我认识你”的地方。在
where you can shake a hand, but the
那里你可以和他们握手，但
interest of just knowing you because of
仅仅是认识你本身就是一种兴趣。 从
the place from the star, it allows a
星空下看，这个地方给了我们一个
moment for the conversation of, "So what
契机，可以聊聊“
is it that you do?"
你是做什么的？”我的
Oh my god. Like that's that's so cool. I
天哪。这太酷了。我
would love to learn more about that. And
很想了解更多。
what you'll find is that the resources
你会发现，
of opportunity over there are endless.
那里的机会资源无穷无尽。
Oh my god. Are you serious? We would
我的天哪。你是认真的吗？我们很
love to partner with you in something
乐意在这样的项目上与你合作
like this. I mean, in this space, are
。我的意思是，在这个领域，
you talking about mental health,
你是在谈论心理健康、
wellness? Listen, strong voices and
福祉吗？听着，我们需要强有力的、
confident voices or inspiring voices.
自信的、鼓舞人心的声音。我们
There could be a lot for us in what we
在这里所做的一切或许能为我们带来很多帮助
do here. Hey, maybe there's a
。嘿，也许
partnership that we can form. Oh my god,
我们可以建立合作关系。我的天哪
man. Back to school kids. I love kids.
。孩子们又要开学了。我喜欢孩子。
I'm thinking about doing more like
我正在考虑做更多类似的
here's something where I think I can
事情，我觉得我可以
have a very very good cadence and a and
很好地把握节奏，用
a very good energy towards getting kids
积极的心态激发孩子们
hype about school education because it's
对学校教育的热情，因为
not something that I took serious. How
我以前并没有认真对待这件事。
do I help? Where did you learn? So when
我该如何提供帮助？你是从哪里学到的？当
I look at this graph here, I see this
我看到这张图表时，我看到了这样一个
sort of moment where things become go up
时刻：事物
and to the right very quickly where you
迅速地向右上方上升。 你
start to get into entrepreneurship. But
开始涉足创业领域。但
at this moment that comes before it, you
在那之前，你对
didn't know this stuff. So at some point
这些一无所知。所以，
you acquired information. So for the
你后来逐渐积累了这些信息。
people that are listening now that are
现在正在听的人可能在
thinking like how did Kevin go from a
想，凯文怎么从一个生活
kid that was in this rough area, dad
在贫困地区、父亲
wasn't around much, his mom was raising
不常在家、由母亲抚养长大的孩子，变成
him to a guy that knows all this stuff.
一个精通所有这些领域的人呢？答案是：
&gt;&gt; You get there now by being a sponge and
你要像海绵一样吸收知识，并且
not being afraid to ask questions. I am
不害怕提问。我
in myself
对自己很有信心，
and being the dummy in the room.
即使我是个“傻瓜”，
I am extremely secure and saying I don't
我也会毫不犹豫地说“我不
know what that means.
知道那是什么意思”。“
Explain that.
请解释一下。
&gt;&gt; Give me an example of a context where
给我举个例子，比如
you
风险
investing.
投资之类的。”
I was a firm believer that nobody's
我坚信，没有人会
stealing my money
偷走我的钱，
and giving you nothing.
然后什么也不给你。
Yeah. You going to go and put it where?
是啊，你会把钱藏到哪里去？
[laughter] Yeah. No, my money going to
（笑）是啊，我的钱就放在
stay right here under my bed. I'm not
床底下。我不会
doing that. So give you you want me to
那样做。所以，如果你想让我
give you money and you telling me you
给你钱，你告诉我你会
going to get you going to take that
拿走这些
money and then that money is going to
钱，然后这些钱会
turn into what? Yeah.
变成什么？ 是啊。
Okay. Go find you another idiot cuz it
好吧。去找另一个傻瓜吧，
ain't happening over here, buddy. Get
伙计，这行不通。赶紧滚蛋。
your scamming ass up out of here. Okay.
好吧。
I come from the world of everything is a
我来自一个万物皆
scam. Okay. It's a [__] scam. I know
骗局的世界。好吧。这他妈就是个骗局。我一眼就能看出
a scam when I see one. All right. But
骗局。好吧。但是
when you go, you say, "Well, how does
当你问，“
the stock market really work?" Or, "How
股市到底是怎么运作的？”或者，“
does investing really work?" Or, "What
投资到底是怎么运作的？”或者，“你说睡觉也能
do you mean you make money while you
赚钱是什么意思
sleeping?" What does that mean? What do
？”这是什么意思？
you mean by that? How does this brand
你这话是什么意思？这种品牌
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
partnership [__] really work? Like, you
合作到底是怎么运作的？
you can't be afraid
你不能害怕
to like verbalize your ignorance.
承认自己的无知。
And and the bigger problem,
而且更大的问题，
[clears throat] which I'm sure a lot of
[清嗓子]我相信
your viewers
你的很多观众
have,
都有这个问题，
is like insecurely like just being quiet
就是缺乏安全感，对不懂的东西保持沉默，
as if you're going to figure it out
好像总有一天会弄明白似的，
because someday, one day, somebody's
因为总有一天，会有人说，“
going to go, "Hey, you look like you
嘿，你看上去
need to know."
需要……”  “知道。”
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声] 这种情况永远
&gt;&gt; It'll never happen that way. It's never
不会发生。永远不会
going to happen. You're never going to
发生。你永远不会
run into a person who's randomly going
遇到一个会随机
to talk about the things that you wish
跟你谈论你希望
you had more knowledge in. It will never
了解更多的事情的人。永远不会
happen. And what you'll find is that
发生。你会发现，
information is not free, but it's
信息并非免费，但它是
available.
存在的。
It's not actually hard to obtain. It's
获取信息其实并不难。
only hard to people that are very
只有那些不
insecure about just verbalizing
自信到不敢说“
I don't know where to get it.
我不知道从哪里获取”的人才会觉得难。
Look at how many howto's help to all of
看看现在有多少教程在帮助人们解决这些
these things today. the the success that
问题。
we're seeing in entrepreneur and
我们在企业家、网红、
influencer streamer and all of this
主播以及所有
stuff in entertainment is the same
娱乐领域看到的成功，与
success that you're seeing in
你在那些
we can call them motivational speakers,
我们可以称之为励志演讲者、
howto experts, uh step one through five
教程专家、一步到第五步教你
and what to do. The idea of I'm here to
做什么的成功是一样的。他们的理念是：我来为
service you and give you the information
你服务，给你提供
that you don't know is available. So,
你不知道的信息。所以，
let me tell you how to get it.
让我告诉你如何获取。
Here's what I'm going to help you. three
这就是我将要帮助你的。三个
easy steps to making sure that you can
简单的步骤，确保你能……
and I don't care if you want to go to
不管你是想进入
the world of athletics or you want to go
体育界、
to corporate or you want to go to
商界还是娱乐界，我都无所谓。就拿高尔夫来说吧，
golf do you know how much money is being
你知道高尔夫这项运动能赚多少钱吗？
made in a game of golf because you got
因为有
millions of people that are trying to
成千上万的人在教
give people information on how to better
别人如何
improve your golf swing cuz I don't want
改进高尔夫挥杆。我不想承认，
to I don't want to say out loud my swing
我不想大声说我的挥杆烂透了，
ain't [__] but I don't know Man, I keep
但我真的不知道。老兄，我总是击球时杆头压在
coming down on top of the ball. Why the
球的上方。我到底为什么会这样
ball? I don't know what's happening. And
？我不知道是怎么回事。
some people would rather go out in their
有些人宁愿每天去自家
backyard every day, hit the same ball,
后院，对着同一个球挥杆，也不愿意
then just ask somebody, "Hey man, any
问别人：“嘿，哥们儿，
way that you can tell me [laughter] how
你能不能告诉我[笑声]该怎么挥杆
to come like what? How do you get that
？”  “怎么才能让那
[__] in the air?" So now people online
婊子飞起来？”现在网上的人
go, well, we're just going to put it out
都想，好吧，我们就把它公开出来，让那些默默
here and that person that's struggling
挣扎的人
quietly where they're going to discover
发现
me and in silence they'll watch and
我，然后他们会在悄悄中观察，努力
they'll look to improve because nobody
改进，因为没人
knows
知道，
and they still get to be quiet.
他们还能继续保持安静。
That's the problem.
这就是问题所在。
Just give me a minute of your time and
请给我一分钟时间，
I'll tell you about a device that my
我来介绍一下我们
team's been using that they won't seem
团队一直在用的一个设备，他们似乎对它
to shut up about. It's called the Note
赞不绝口。它叫Note
Pro and it's by our sponsor Plaude. This
Pro，是我们的赞助商Plaude的产品。这个
tiny card clips onto the back of your
小卡片可以夹在
phone and captures everything. But why
手机背面，记录所有内容。
it's so clever is that it picks up
它最巧妙的地方在于可以
multiple voices at the same time. And
同时捕捉多个声音。当
when someone says something important,
有人说了什么重要的话，
you just push this tiny little button
你只需按下这个小按钮，
here and that moment gets highlighted in
那一刻就会在你的笔记中被高亮显示
your notes and captured. It records the
并记录下来。它会记录
conversations that it hears, takes those
听到的对话，
conversations, creates a transcript, and
生成文字稿，并
it uses AI to synthesize all of that
利用人工智能将所有
information into whatever template suits
信息合成到你喜欢的任何模板中
you. You get a summary, action points,
。你会收到一份摘要、行动要点、
highlights, and even a mind map sent
高亮显示，甚至还有思维导图，
straight to the Plaude app. So, I highly
直接发送到你的邮箱。 去看看Plaude app吧。所以我强烈
recommend you check out Plaude's
建议你点击下方描述中的链接，看看Plaude的
products using the link in the
产品
description below. Don't tell anybody
。别告诉别人
this, but if you use code DOAC22,
，如果你使用优惠码DOAC22，
you'll get 22% off on some of Plaude's
就能享受Plaude部分产品22%的折扣
products. There's also unknown unknowns,
。还有一些
which you would have experienced. I
你肯定经历过的未知未知。我
remember you talking about um you got to
记得你说过，你
see behind curtains and you didn't even
看到了窗帘后面，却根本不
know people were behind there. And when
知道有人在那里。当
when I heard you say that, it was the
我听到你说这话的时候，我觉得这简直就是
what I had experienced in my life.
我人生经历的完美比喻。我
Coming from a kid that came from a very
来自一个非常
normal background, was was born in
普通的家庭，出生在
Africa, moved to the UK, mother's
非洲，后来搬到英国，母亲是
Nigerian, dad's English, and didn't know
尼日利亚人，父亲是英国人，我以前根本不知道
that all these like rich people were
这些有钱人在
back here playing money games. I thought
这里玩弄金钱游戏。我以前以为
the way you make money is you like work
赚钱的方式就是
in McDonald's, you like work really
在麦当劳打工，
hard, you might become manager, D. And
努力工作，也许能升到经理什么的。
then at like I'm going to say 27 being
然后，大概27岁的时候，我
sat in a billionaire's kitchen and
坐在一个亿万富翁的厨房里，
watching him on the phone and he's
看着他打电话…… 他
calling his boy and they're doing 50
打电话给他儿子，说要在
million just before the IPO happens so
IPO前搞个5000万美元的交易，这样就能
that they get a better price and I'm
拿到更好的价格。我当时
thinking [__] hell.
就想，我的天哪。
the the the thing that I've realized
我意识到，
right when you look at your biggest
当你审视你最大的
investors right
投资人时，
you'll find that they're all together.
你会发现他们都聚在一起。
None of them are investing in the new
他们中没有一个人会单独投资新
thing alone.
项目。
They all are like, "Well, it's better
他们都说：“有
with you,
你参与更好，
so do it with me." Well, what about
所以跟我一起做吧。” 那加里呢
Gary? Yeah, call Gary, too. Let's see if
？对，也给加里打个电话。看看能
we can get him in here. What about
不能把他拉进来。
Michelle? Yeah. Hey, Michelle. What
米歇尔呢？对。嗨，米歇尔。
about Melissa? All right. You'll find
梅丽莎呢？好的。你会发现，
that this group of 10 people all who
这十个人，他们本来
could easily do something on their own
都能独立完成一些事情，
do not believe in the struggles of self
却不相信单打独斗，
when you can combine
而应该把
this machine of great minds
这些优秀的人才聚集起来，
to provide another great opportunity and
创造另一个绝佳的机会，获得
in success. Well, this thing works. The
成功。这样一来，
company gets bigger. Well, let's use our
公司就能发展壮大。那么，我们就应该利用我们的
resources to go out and make sure that
资源，把
we align the person that they already
现有员工和
have with more amazing individuals,
更多优秀的人才结合起来，
create more jobs, more opportunities for
创造更多就业机会。 更多的
new minds to become successful. And then
新人才有机会获得成功。然后，
in those minds building and that
在这些人才的培养和
personnel like elevating,
人员的提升过程中，
well, now this person that was at the
比如，我们让原本处于底层的人来管理公司
person to run this thing. And now
。现在，在公司
underneath this thing we get another
底层，我们迎来了新一轮的人才涌入
version of a downpour.
。
New minds, new personnel, new things.
新的人才、新的人员、新的事物。
Okay, this whole business of venture,
好吧，风险投资和
this whole business of company build,
公司建设的整个过程，
whether it's tech, lifestyle, health,
无论是科技、生活方式还是健康，都
well, it doesn't matter what it is. You
无关紧要。你
will notice that the people that started
会发现，那些从底层做起的人
from the bottom are now running the new
现在正在管理着
companies of today. And now the source
今天的新公司。而公司
of personnel that's underneath it will
底层的人才，将
be the minds running the company of
成为未来公司的领导者
tomorrow.
。
It's not like rocket science. Once
这并不复杂。一旦
you're behind the curtain
你了解了真相，你就会恍然大悟。
I remember when when I first started
我记得我刚开始
like investing this, "Oh my god, Kevin,
投资的时候，“我的天哪，凯文，你投资的
like your your money in this would add a
钱会创造
crazy amount of value." Well, I ain't
巨大的价值。”好吧，我
putting in what y'all put in. No, but
投入的资金肯定比不上你们。不，但
the fact that you're involved in it at
你们参与其中
all is just big that you believe in it
本身就意义重大，说明你们相信它。
and we're able to say that you believe
我们能说你相信
in it with us is huge.
我们，这意义重大。
What do you mean by that? [laughter]
你这话是什么意思？[笑声]
You trying to [__] steal? What are
你想偷东西？
you doing? What are you doing, man? You
你在干什么？你在干什么，伙计？你
talking too fast. Say what you said
说话太快了。再说一遍
again. Slow down so I understand it.
。慢点，这样我才能听懂。
Don't talk fast to me because I'm so
别跟我说话这么快，因为我没
insecure cuz I don't know what you're
安全感，我听不懂你在
saying and it might be some [__] in
说什么，这里面可能都是些乱七八糟的东西
here.
。
But it's No. Well,
但不是。
we know that you're you're doing well
我们知道你在这里做得很好，
over here and your movies and all that
你的电影什么的都
stuff is cool, but this is different.
很棒，但这不一样。
This business, Kevin, could be different
凯文，这个行业
for you. It's a business of multiple. So
对你来说可能不一样。这是一个倍数的行业。所以
we play a game of multiples of X. So
我们玩的是倍数游戏。那么你
what your money is today? Well, we think
现在有多少钱？嗯，我们认为，
in success if this is a light bulb or a
如果这是一个灯泡或
bottle rocket, you 30X, 20X. What the
瓶装火箭，那么成功就是30倍、20倍。什么
[__] You're telling me that if I put
鬼？你是说，如果我
this money in here right now, and if my
现在把这些钱投进去，如果我的
voice is attached to the thing that I
声音与我认为的这个项目联系在一起，那会怎样？
think it is, which is a crazy
这是一个疯狂的
crazy venture, a crazy opportunity.
冒险，一个疯狂的冒险 机会。
Well, yeah, Kevin. I mean, look, we all
嗯，是的，凯文。我的意思是，你看，我们都
believe that, but with your voice, we
相信这一点，但有了你的声音，我们
may be able to say it a little louder.
或许可以更大声地表达出来。
Oh my.
哦，我的天。哦，我的天。
Oh my. Okay. Well, I did it. Oh my. I I
好吧。我做到了。哦，我的天。我
won. I got a return. Oh my.
赢了。我得到了回报。哦，我的天。哦。哦。
So, now I figured it out. Now, now
所以，现在我明白了。现在，
you're part of the right conversations.
你参与了正确的对话。
You're part of the the right
你抓住了正确的
opportunities. But once again,
机会。但再一次，
the information is discovered
信息的发现是
because of the opportunity to be the
因为有机会成为
you never imagined yourself being in.
你从未想象过自己会身处的空间里的一朵花。
But now, look at what I'm able to do.
但现在，看看我能做什么。
I'm able to take this information, take
我能够利用这些信息，利用
all the [__] that I know, come and have
我所知道的一切，来参与这些
these [__] organic conversations like
像
I am now. And we're sharing it. And some
我现在这样自然而然的对话。我们正在分享这些信息。一些
people that are watching this are going
正在观看的人会
to take that information and go, I knew
接受这些信息，然后说，我就知道
it.
。
and I'm doing the right thing and it's a
我做的是对的，我
matter of time before I get around them.
接触到他们只是时间问题。
And when I do, oh my god, the things
当我接触到他们时，哦，我的天，
that I have, the stuff that I have on
我拥有的东西，我拥有的那些东西……
the table, the things that I have
这张桌子，我
created, the opportunities,
创造的一切，这些机会，
I'mma be the next person to bring the
我将成为下一个把
thing that everybody else is involved
大家都在参与的事情带进来的人
in. I'mma be the next person to be the
。我将成为下一个为
[__] energy source to tomorrow's
未来注入能量的人
future future within. like people just
。人们只
need to hear
需要知道
how fast it happens, quick it happens,
这一切发生得有多快，有多迅速，
and and and when it does what you're
以及当它发生时，你
supposed to be ready for.
应该做好准备。
&gt;&gt; And you were able to invest in lots of
你投资了很多
great companies like Function Health,
很棒的公司，比如Function Health，
that's valued at 2.5 billion now. 11
现在估值25亿美元。还有11
Labs, everybody knows in the tech space,
Labs，科技圈人尽皆知的
those 11 Labs, which were valued valued
11 Labs，
at three billion now, Moonpay, um
现在估值30亿美元，Moonpay，
&gt;&gt; Young Labs, Sweat Pals, Radiant,
Young Labs，Sweat Pals，Radiant，
Noranics, Paltown, um
Noranics，Paltown，还有
&gt;&gt; tons of stuff stuff that you would never
很多你绝对
expect me to be in. How much of this
想不到我会涉足的公司。
game have you learned in hindsight is
事后看来，你从这场游戏中学到了多少东西？这关乎
people about like getting because even
人们如何理解，因为即使
when that person was saying to you that
有人跟你说了你
analogy you gave of they're telling you
举的那个比喻，他们让你
to put your money into this thing and
把钱投到某个项目上，而
you're going [__] me are they stealing
你却在想“我去，他们是不是在骗我”，
you're going to have to lean on someone
你仍然会…… 你需要依靠
you trust like someone in your circle
你信任的人，比如你圈子里认识的人。
&gt;&gt; and I'm I'm wondering cuz people don't
我一直在想，因为人们很少
talk about it enough how how important
谈论这一点，那就是找到
&gt;&gt; collect the right people and can you
合适的人有多么重要。你能
think of moments where you like met a
想起那些你遇到某
person and that was like gamechanging
个人，然后人生发生翻天覆地变化，让
and you understanding a whole new world
你了解一个全新的世界，看到
and what was behind the curtain.
幕后真相的时刻吗？我身边的
&gt;&gt; All of my people could see this. I'm I'm
人都能理解这一点。我只想
just going to be extremely transparent.
坦诚地说，
before you get to the right people, you
在你遇到合适的人之前，你会
run through wrong people.
遇到一些不合适的人。
with wrong people, you can go like,
遇到不合适的人，你可以说：“他们不对劲，
they're wrong. They don't work. I got to
他们不行，我得
get somebody else. Or you can grow with
找别人。”或者，你可以和
people.
他们一起成长。
I'm a believer of the grow, right? Like
我相信成长，对吧？
I think it's dope when we can all say we
我觉得很棒，我们都能说，我们最初是那样
started a certain way but we're ending
开始的，但最终在
that journey of growth. Some people
成长的旅程中到达了一个完全不同的境地。有些人可能
won't make it. You can be patient and
无法成功。你可以耐心等待，
you can want the best for some but they
你可以希望他们一切都好，但他们
might not want the same for themselves.
可能并不这么想。
So because of that the falloff
正因为如此，这种转变才会显得
presents itself to be a little more
更加
consistent um than what it should be.
稳定，而不是…… 应该如此。
Right. Mhm.
没错。嗯。
&gt;&gt; But in business, what you'll find
但在商业中，你会发现
is that the emotions
情绪
can be your like
有时会
can be your worst asset. Having emotions
成为你最大的劣势。
in business attached to business
在商业中，情绪与商业紧密相连，
can be everything but beneficial to the
对企业来说绝非好事
business. So the more that I was able to
。因此，我越能将
detach my emotions
自己的情绪
from the world of want and understand
从欲望的世界中抽离出来，越能理解
that the things that I'm doing are to
我所做的一切都是为了
better position the business
更好地定位企业，
and the people that have worked so hard
以及那些为
to help this business get to where it is
企业发展到
today. I have a service to them as well.
今天这一步而辛勤付出的人们。我也在为他们提供服务。
How do I bring in the right valuable
我该如何引进合适的
assets to put us in a bigger position to
人才，让我们在竞争中占据更有利的地位
win? Sometimes you got to let go
？有时你必须放弃
of things that you thought would be the
那些你认为会
thing, but you can you can climax. You
奏效的东西，但你可能会达到瓶颈。你
can you can get to a place where it's a
可能会遇到瓶颈，
ceiling. You're like, we're not getting
你会觉得，
past the ceiling unless we go get the
除非我们找到
right people, unless we go get the
合适的人才，除非我们找到
correct personnel. So, I'm a firm
合适的员工，否则我们无法突破瓶颈。所以，我
believer in talent. I'm a firm believer
坚信人才的重要性。我坚信应该
in rewarding those that do a job and
奖励那些能够出色
that can do a job at a high level. But
完成工作的人。但
the only way to you realize that is to
你只有通过努力才能意识到这一点。 别
get out of the way. I had to learn to
碍事。我必须学会
stop trying to control everything. Stop
不再试图控制一切，不再
trying to do everything. Stop trying to
试图包揽一切，不再事事亲力亲为，而是让
everything and put people in a position
人们各司其职，
to do the thing that they've been hired
做好他们被雇佣来做的事情
to do and do it well. But the patience
。但
that you have to have
你必须要有耐心，
and learning people and dealing with
了解他人，与
people is a talent within itself. I want
人打交道，这本身就是一种天赋。我
to say like you're
想说，就像你现在所处的
at this stage I'm more
阶段，我更像是一个存储
of other people's issues or problems
他人问题或麻烦的硬盘，而不是
than I am a person. [laughter]
一个人。[笑声]
I I am a hard drive of can I talk to
我就像一个硬盘，里面装着“我可以跟你谈谈吗
you? I want to tell you what's going on.
？我想告诉你发生了什么事。
I have an issue with. Hey man, look, I'm
我遇到了问题。嘿，伙计，听着，我正在
trying to do this. I don't know what
努力做这件事。我不知道
they trying to do. Here's what I'm
他们想做什么。这就是我正在
trying to do. And you have to be a
努力做的。”你必须
positive source of solution all day,
每天都成为积极的解决方案提供者
every day. Because if you're talking and
。因为如果你说话只是为了做事而不是
you're talking to do anything but solve,
解决问题，
then you shouldn't be in the chair of
那么你就不应该坐在
control. So I am solutiondriven
控制的位置上。所以我
every single day because I am faced with
每天都以解决问题为导向，因为我面临着……
and the community that I built
我建立的生态系统和社群面临着一个新的问题：
underneath me of how to navigate or how
如何
to better navigate in the world because
在这个世界上更好地生存，因为
everybody's trying to do something to
每个人都想证明
prove that they're worthy of the seat or
自己配得上他们所
seats that they have or that they want.
拥有或渴望的席位。
So every day
所以，
you're dealing with a board of shuffle
你每天都要面对一个不断变化的局面，一个充满
and a new board of opportunity
机遇
&gt;&gt; and drama.
和挑战的局面。
&gt;&gt; And every day you're telling people not
你每天都要告诉别人：
now and time. Slow up. I hear you. We'll
现在还不是时候。慢点说：我明白你的意思。我们会处理的
deal with it. Let's all talk together.
。大家一起谈谈。
Communication is key. Let's table this
沟通是关键。先把这件事搁置，
and make sure everybody's on the same
确保每个人都理解一致
page. you're saying things five and six
。你一遍遍地重复同一句话，
times because you have to make sure that
确保
you're the best example of what you're
自己能做到
speaking.
言行一致。
So every day
所以，
the thing that you never thought would
你从未想过会发挥作用的，
is communication
就是沟通，
and like the ability to [__] give
以及进行
great dialogue in the hopes of getting
有效对话的能力，希望能够获得
the return of effort and work. So now
努力和工作的回报。现在，
you're going back to ground zero when
你又回到了最初的起点，回到了
you were with your mom and you were with
你和妈妈、
your friends in the early days of life.
朋友们一起度过的童年时光。
And what was the thing that I told you I
我之前说过我
did very well? I connected with
做得非常好的是什么？我和
everybody in a lunchroom. I was at
每个人都建立了良好的关系。 在餐厅里，我坐在
everybody's table. Didn't matter who you
每个人的桌子上。无论你
were, what you were, what race, what
是谁，你的身份，你的种族，
didn't matter in this space of now
在这个
business and corporation. If everybody
商业和公司里，这些都不重要。如果每个人都
doesn't feel like they can trust or
觉得他们无法信任、
believe or follow
相信或追随
my direction, my vision, something about
我的方向和愿景，那么
what I'm doing is wrong.
我所做的事情肯定有问题。
&gt;&gt; How does one build an empire that relies
一个人如何建立一个依赖
on people when they naturally
于他人的商业帝国，而这些人本身
don't come from a place of that
并不具备这种能力
information? So they they might have
？所以他们可能会有
trust issues like you were referring to
信任问题，就像你刚才提到的
these kind of trust issues like wait a
那种信任危机，比如“
minute, you're trying to steal my money.
等等，你这是要偷我的钱吗？”。
How does you've got this big empire of
你如何才能在
within Heartbeat and your your companies
Heartbeat、你的公司
and your personal IP. You're going to
以及你的个人知识产权中建立起如此庞大的商业帝国？你必须把
people with your wealth, with your
你的财富、你的
business, and with your with your
事业，甚至你
children's inheritance. And I hear so
孩子的遗产都托付给很多人。我听过太多
many of these stories of I trusted a guy
这样的故事：我信任了一个人，
and I lost everything. Especially
结果失去了一切。说
honestly, especially in the like black
实话，尤其是在黑人
community.
社区。嗯，
&gt;&gt; It's a major fact. Um, but we're also a
这是个不争的事实。但是，我们也是一个容易被人
gets taken advantage of
利用的群体，
because of the lack of knowledge, right?
因为…… 就是因为缺乏知识，对吧？
We get [__] over more than we don't
我们被坑的次数比没被坑的次数多得多，
because
因为
All right. Well, it says here that
……好吧，这里写着
you're a lawyer and that you have my
你是律师，你会为我
best interest. All right. It says that
着想。好吧，这里写着
you're my manager and you have my best
你是我的经理，你会为我
interest.
着想。
All right. Well, you read the paperwork.
好吧，你读了文件。好吧，
All right. You read the contract and
你读了合同，没问题，
it's good and I'm just signing, right?
我就签字了，对吧？
My ignorance doesn't mean that I'm lazy.
我的无知并不代表我懒惰。
My ignorance means that I believe you.
我的无知意味着我相信你。
I don't know to second guessess or
我不知道该如何质疑、
second check or to hire or onboard
复核，或者在招聘或入职新
people to second guess to second check
员工时，如何质疑、复核，以便向
to show me
我指出那些
fine print fine line because it's
细则和漏洞，因为这是
impossible. I can't get [__] cuz you
不可能的。我不会被坑，因为你
said
说，是的，
well yeah I can't but you said
我不会，但你说要
go back to the emotions and why I say
回归情感，这就是为什么我说
emotions had to be removed. I'm going to
必须排除情感因素。我会找
have somebody look at this just so I
人看看，这样我才能确定
know that it is what it is. I wouldn't
它到底是什么。我不会
lie to you. I know. But it's in the best
对你撒谎。我知道。但从
nature of business just for me to make
商业角度来说，
sure that my eyes that I have lay eyes
确保我亲眼所见是理所当然的。
on it and they can just say what you
他们只要看了就能说出你
just said but just make sure I
刚才说的那些话，但你得确保我
understand it correctly. Yeah. But you
理解正确。是啊。不过你
don't have to do that. It's nothing
没必要这么做。这并非
against you. It's just a practice that I
针对你。这只是我
have within the way that I now approach
现在处理
business and anything that you do. It's
生意和你做的任何事的一种习惯。这
never personal. I don't take offense to
绝非针对你个人。如果
anything that you want to check or
你想查
background check on me. You should. It's
我的资料或背景，我不会生气。你应该生气。这是
business.
生意。
I think that
我觉得
we don't get a fair level of
我们
understanding for our fuckups, for our
对自己犯的错、我们的
mishaps, of how the road presented
失误，以及
itself for somebody to take from me. So
别人是如何利用我的机会的，并没有得到应有的理解。所以，
when I'm recovering from the take,
当我从被利用的打击中恢复过来时
well, you got to start at a safe space.
，你必须先找到一个安全的地方。
My space was never safe because they're
我的空间从来都不安全，因为他们都是
sharks. So they focus on the [__]
鲨鱼。所以他们只关注
prey. The young talent in the music
猎物。音乐界的年轻人才
business is prey.
就是猎物。
So the sharks see the young talent.
所以鲨鱼们会盯上这些年轻人才。谁先
Whichever one gets there first
下手为强，谁就
has an opportunity
有机会把
to [__] give me the presentation of
我捧上天，让我眼花缭乱
and candy. Well, if I get there right
。如果我能抓住机会，
and the prey doesn't have the right
而猎物没能抓住，那我就有机会了。 只要
people around them, I'm going with the
身边有合适的人，我
shark every time.
每次都愿意跟鲨鱼一起走。
&gt;&gt; I guess you there is an element of
我觉得这
responsibility here which people don't
里面确实存在责任因素，只是人们
like to acknowledge that you got to take
不愿意承认，你必须承担
responsibility. I signed bad contracts
责任。我职业生涯中签过一些糟糕的合同，
in my career and I was like I look back
回想
at 20 years I go [__] you know I lost
20年前，我心想，我当时损失惨重
a lot there. But that was on me and if I
。但那是我自己的责任，如果我
don't take responsibility then it's
不承担责任，这种事还会
going to happen again. But there's also
再次发生。但
you you'll know a lot of people that
你也会认识很多
become victims. I don't think it's the
受害者。我觉得这并非
worst thing, right? Like it's when it
最糟糕的事，对吧？尤其是在
happens early on. Like I got a lot of
早期就遭遇这种情况的时候。我有很多
friends that are in the music business,
朋友在音乐圈，
a lot of artists that are now
很多艺人现在都是
independent artists that control and own
独立音乐人，他们掌控着
their labels and are doing much better
自己的厂牌，现在的发展
at this position than they were when
比以前
they were signed underneath the big
签约大
thing. And they were getting taken, but
公司时好得多。他们以前被大公司坑过，但在
after finding out how it was and why it
弄清真相和原因后，
was, they said, "I'm going to go create
他们说：“我要
my own." Like, you know, when you look
自己创业。” 你知道，当你看看
at the biggest labels that are
那些最大的
independent and you look at the artists
独立厂牌，再看看
that fall underneath these independent
这些独立
labels, well, you'll look at a blueprint
厂牌旗下的艺人，你会发现…… 你会看到这样的模式：
of people following
人们追随
&gt;&gt; the person that was like in front of
前面的人，听从
them and what they said, but it was only
他们的话，但这仅仅是
because they learned the business of the
因为他们学会了这
business, right? Like so being a part of
行的运作方式，对吧？就像加入一个
a business that's just succeeding and
成功的企业，
you being embedded into it
融入其中，
&gt;&gt; and just being the work for hire that
成为他们的雇佣兵，
just follows the suit what they say.
照搬他们的说辞。
Well that's not smart if you have an
如果你有
opportunity to mirror what they're doing
机会模仿他们的做法，
and create your own. So what I do like
创造属于自己的事业，那这样做就不明智了。我喜欢的一种
within a culture is a lot of the artists
文化是，很多
that are that are independent or that
独立艺术家，或者
are that are now like
现在
able to say I have my own version
能够说“我拥有自己的版本”的艺术家，
whether it's studio production company
无论是工作室、制作公司、
label independent label whether it's own
独立厂牌，还是与他人
line of product that they share
共享所有权的自有产品线，
ownership with like people are now
现在人们都在
learning to follow and and repeat what
学习如何效仿和复制
the conglomerates are doing. I can use a
大公司的做法。我可以利用
conglomerate and I can take your machine
大公司的资源，
underneath yours and partner with you
在你的体系下创建一个小型版本，与你合作，
and give you a piece of my machine, but
给你一部分资源，但这
it allows me to own I can leverage the
让我拥有所有权，我可以利用
that you have here under this brand.
你品牌下的机会和消费者资源。
&gt;&gt; What's the cost though? Because you
成本是什么？ 不过呢？因为你
know, you're incredibly successful.
知道，你非常成功。
You've got all this empire of companies
你拥有庞大的公司
and businesses and ventures you've
、企业和创业帝国
started. They say that you can't have
。人们常说人生不可能拥有
everything in life,
一切，
&gt;&gt; especially not at the same time.
尤其不可能同时拥有。
&gt;&gt; So, what is the cost of this pursuit?
那么，追求这一切的代价是什么？
Because
是
&gt;&gt; time.
时间。
&gt;&gt; Time.
你的野心是不是永无止境？
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。它就是不会
off if you wanted to.
停止。就算你想关掉也关不掉。
&gt;&gt; And does that not make you feel like
这难道不让你感觉
you're being dragged versus being
自己是被拖着走而不是被
driven?
驱动吗？
&gt;&gt; You for sure have your days. I'm
你当然也有状态不好的时候。我
absolutely stressed out. I'm stressed
压力山大。我
the [__] out on the daily, but I operate
每天都压力山大，但我能在
within stress.
压力下工作。
&gt;&gt; Are you happy?
你快乐吗？
&gt;&gt; I'm 10,000% happy, but I'm stressed out
我百分之万快乐，但我被“
with the concept of I have to do.
我必须做”这个概念压得喘不过气来。
&gt;&gt; If your life ended now, God forbid.
如果你的生命现在就结束了，天哪，千万别这样。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; Do do you think if you if you found out
你觉得如果你
today that it was ending, you would
今天才知道生命即将结束，你会不会
reflect on it and say, do you know, I
反思一下，然后说，你知道吗，
think I might have had things in the
我可能把事情的
wrong order, would there be any mis
顺序搞错了，
prioritization in hindsight if today was
如果今天就结束了，事后看来，会不会有什么优先级错误？ 就是
the day? If life ended today,
今天吗？如果生命今天终结，
I could cross my legs comfortably
我可以安心地翘起二郎腿，坦然
and be okay.
接受。是
That it's that it's time. I did it
时候了。我做得
correctly. I
对。我
made sure that I applied myself to the
确保自己竭尽所能
best of my ability.
。
I tried my best to put those that I
我尽力让我
loved in a better position so that they
爱的人处于更好的境地，让他们
could see more and do more.
能看到更多，做更多。
My last name and my family name is much
我的姓氏和家族名声
stronger today than it was yesterday.
今天比昨天更加响亮。
the world is something that I was able
我能够更好地理解这个世界，
because I was blessed and fortunate
因为我有幸
enough to travel and meet so many
旅行，结识了那么多人，他们就像
are made to like we're here to embrace,
我们来到这个世界是为了拥抱，为了
we're here to love, we're here to like
爱，为了
share.
分享。
&gt;&gt; Mhm. [clears throat]
嗯。[清嗓子]
I was an energy source of good to bring
我曾是善良的能量源泉，
people closer together through all
通过我所做的一切，将人们联系在一起
things that I've done. So, it all
。所以，一切都
connects. And I'm okay.
息息相关。我没事。
I'm okay with if it stopped, it stopped.
如果生命就此结束，我也能接受。但
What I'm what I'm not okay with is while
我不能接受的是，当
I have the bandwidth of good health,
我拥有健康的身体、
[__] great mind, strong
强大的思维能力、坚定的
[__] like mind concept and I can I
信念，并且能够
can go I can do it. I can get there.
继续前行的时候，我却无法做到。 到达那里。
I'm not okay with wasting that time.
我不愿浪费时间。
I'm not okay with wasting my time of
我不愿浪费我
good and I can do and I'm strong enough
美好的时光，我能做到，而且我足够强大，可以与
to connect at a very high level. My star
高层次的人建立联系。我的星光
is bright which allows me to go and get
璀璨，这让我能够
into these spaces. If I wait for this to
进入这些领域。如果我等到这股热潮
dim out and I try to get into these
消退才去尝试进入这些
spaces, what if I can't?
领域，万一我做不到呢？你是否总是
&gt;&gt; Is there always a fear because of where
因为自己的
you came from that the stuff absolutely
出身而害怕这一切终将
might dim?
消逝？
&gt;&gt; Absolutely. Like you you can't be
当然。就像你一样，你不能
unrealistic.
不切实际。没有什么会永远持续下去
Nothing is going to last forever.
。没有什么。
nothing. I don't give a [__] who you
我不在乎你
are. I don't It's not true. You can
是谁。我不在乎。这不是真的。你可以不断
recreate and you can figure out ways to
重塑自我，你可以找到方法
find success again
一次又一次地获得成功
and again,
，
but the one thing that you are winning
但你唯一正在获胜的领域
in, you're not going to win in it
，你不可能
forever, right? Like
永远获胜，对吧？就像
I love talking about my guy man Hoveve
我喜欢谈论我的朋友Hoveve
and Ruben, Michael Rubin. like
和Ruben，Michael Rubin。他们是
two great [clears throat]
两位很棒的
friends but two good examples
朋友，也是两个很好的例子，他们通过不断重复、放大和重复，
and step repeat right successful rapper
成功地制作了说唱歌手的
albums some albums hope will never make
专辑，有些专辑你希望永远不要
again some will you don't look at them
再制作，有些专辑你不会再制作。 把他们都看作是
all like they are all the best some you
最棒的，有些你
think are better than others but the
觉得比其他的更好，但想要重现
it was at your highest
巅峰时期的自己，
is a driving factor to get you. But then
才是你前进的动力。但
as a talent, you you let go of that
作为一名天才，你会放下这种执念，
because you become comfortable with
因为你逐渐接受了“
knowing that I'm never going to create
我再也无法创造那样的成就”这个事实
that again. That was my lightning in the
。那就是我的人生。 瓶中之战的
bottle moment. I'm never going to create
时刻。 我再也不会创作出
this again, but I can have fun doing
这样的作品了，但我可以享受创作的过程，
what I'm doing and I can create a
我可以创作出各种
variation
变体
of versions of this that still display
版本，这些版本仍然能够展现
my talent and that I'm doing it at a
我的才华，并且证明我在这方面达到了
high level. Man, you know what? This
很高的水平。 老兄，你知道吗？
right here, it could cap out. But boy oh
到此为止，可能就到此为止了。 但是，哎呀
boy, did I find [__] momentum and now
，我找到了他妈的动力，现在
the movies or in Ho's case is the
电影，或者用何的例子来说，就是
example I was using. He then found
我举的例子。 然后他找到了
momentum and well this thing, the
发展势头，嗯，就是洛克菲勒那件事，
Rockefeller thing, him dame created this
他创造了这
thing and then the artists underneath
件事，然后是这件事下的艺术家们，
the thing and the progression of the
以及
artist underneath that brand and started
这个品牌下艺术家们的发展，然后就开始
to go bow pow Kanye bow state property
火起来，坎耶·韦斯特、State Property、
beanie seagull bow bow bow Rihanna all
Beanie Seagull、蕾哈娜等等
these people bow now this thing was so
这些人，现在这件事
dope that we were able to create other
太棒了，我们能够创造出更多的
people that's more energy so now I don't
人才，这更有活力，所以现在我不需要那些
need the [__] I don't need the
乱七八糟的东西，我不需要那些乱七八糟的东西，
I'm looking at the product of a valuable
我看到的是我们创造的宝贵资产的成果，它
enough to display that the talent that
足够优质，足以证明
comes from underneath us
我们旗下的人才
is strong [__] talent and we do
非常优秀，我们能做出
amazing things. Now my business because
惊人的事情。 现在，因为
of this business well this business
这项业务，我的生意
becomes great too. Ace of spades and
也变得非常好了。 黑桃A和
deuce say and all oh [__] the value the
2说，哦，该死，价值，
exit the return he keeps finding more
退出，回报，他不断从
energy in these other things. Mhm.
这些其他事情中发现更多能量。 嗯。   妈的
&gt;&gt; Oh [__] 4040 club. More assets, more
。  4040俱乐部。 更多资产、更多
brand, likeness, partnership, ownership.
品牌、更多肖像权、更多合作关系、更多所有权。
But the backdrop to it all is the
但这一切的背景是
artists.
艺术家们。
Just give me 15 seconds to explain how
请给我15秒钟时间，让我解释一下如何在
you can build a viable business online.
网上建立一个可行的企业。
The people I see winning in life don't
我所见到的成功人士，都
have a perfect plan. They just take the
没有完美的计划。 他们迈出
first step and then the next and then
第一步，然后迈出下一步，就这样一直
they keep going. They stay obsessed and
走下去。 他们始终保持专注和
they stay consistent. And Standstore, a
坚持。  Standstore 是
platform I co-own and one of our
我共同拥有的平台，也是我们的
sponsors, is the best first step to help
赞助商之一，它是帮助
turn your knowledge into income. It only
你将知识转化为收入的最佳第一步。
takes a couple of minutes to launch your
只需几分钟即可启动您的
business and start selling digital
业务，开始在线销售数字
products, coaching, memberships, or
产品、辅导、会员资格或
communities online without any tech
社区，无需任何技术
headaches or endless setup. Thousands of
难题或无休止的设置。 成千上万的
entrepreneurs, creators, and risktakers
企业家、创造者和冒险家
use Stan to take control of their
使用 Stan 来掌控自己的
future. Because Stan is for
未来。 因为 Stan 是为
entrepreneurs, for those willing to put
创业者准备的，是为那些愿意付出
in the work and bet on themselves. If
努力并相信自己的人准备的。 如果
you're ready to start building, join us.
你准备好开始建设，就加入我们吧。   立即访问
stevenbartlet.stan.store.
stevenbartlet.stan.store，享受 14 天免费试用，开启您的创业之旅。
Have you ever heard about this before?
你以前听说过这件事吗？
This thing I'm holding in my hands now.
我现在手里拿着的就是这个东西。
This is called ketone IQ. The website is
这被称为酮体智商（ketene IQ）。 该网站是
ketone.com. You've heard me on this
ketone.com。 你们可能在这个
podcast talking about the fact that I
播客节目里听我说过，我
stay much of the year in a ketogenic
一年中的大部分时间都处于生酮
state, which is a highly restricted
状态，这是一种高度限制性的
diet. And the reason I do that is
饮食。 我这样做的原因有
plentifold. One of them is I spend hours
很多。 其中之一是我每天要花好几个
and hours talking to people for a
小时与人交谈才能
living. So, I want to make sure my brain
谋生。 所以，我想确保我的大脑
is firing in an optimal way. And the
以最佳状态运转。
other reason that I do the ketogenic
我选择生酮饮食的另一个原因
diet is because I just feel better. So,
是，我感觉身体更好了。 所以，
when I discovered this, which is what
当我发现这种被
they call an exogenous ketone product
称为外源性酮类产品的东西时，
your blood's ketone levels, I was blown
我简直惊呆了。这种产品可以喝下去，提高血液中的酮体水平。
away. I contacted them, I met them, I
我联系了他们，见了他们，对
invested extremely heavily into their
他们的
company and I've become a co-owner of
公司进行了大量投资，因此我成为了公司的共同所有人，
the company accordingly and they sponsor
他们
this show now. So, if you want to try
现在赞助了这个节目。 所以，如果你想
this out for yourself, I recommend you
亲自尝试一下，我建议你
try it. Just visit ketone.com/stephven
试试。 只需访问 ketone.com/stephven，
and you'll get 30% off your first
即可享受首次订阅订单 30% 的折扣
subscription order. You'll also get a
。 第二次发货时，您还将获得一份
free gift with your second shipment.
免费礼物。
That's ketone.com/stephven.
那是 ketone.com/stephven。
Your show is called Your New Well, it's
你的节目叫《你的新井》，但它本身
not new necessarily. I actually saw it
并不一定很新。 我其实是
in in London. Me and my girlfriend were
在伦敦亲眼看到的。 我和我的女朋友在
were near the front row when you came
你来伦敦表演的时候就坐在前排附近，你当时正在表演，扮演的是
and did um acting acting my age in
我这个年纪的人
London. The show was absolutely
。 这部剧真的太
hilarious and we were dying of laughter
搞笑了，我们笑得都快岔气了，
and it's coming to Netflix Monday the
它将于
24th of November. So
11月24日星期一在Netflix上线。 所以，
&gt;&gt; if you're listening now, you've got to
如果你现在正在听，那就一定要
go and watch it. But the title of the
去看。 但是这个节目的标题是《
&gt;&gt; acting my age,
扮演我的年龄》，
&gt;&gt; what does what do you mean acting my
你说的“扮演我的年龄”是什么意思
age? And why now?
？ 为什么是现在？
&gt;&gt; Um, [snorts]
嗯，（嗤笑）
you know, you got to grow up.
你知道，你得长大。
I think it's like one of the
我觉得
in life is just realizing
人生中最难的事情之一就是真正理解“
like what grow up actually means, right?
长大成人”的含义，对吧？
And like you can you can be an adult but
就像你可以是个成年人，但
still not embrace
仍然无法真正理解
what being an adult actually is. And
成为成年人的意义一样。
when it's time to grow up, you start
当到了该长大的时候，你就得
sacrificing
放弃那些
the the [__] that the younger version of
年轻时
you with less responsibilities thrived
责任较轻、赖以生存
and flourished off of. And in you
和发展的东西。 然后你会
realize that a lot of that [__] gets
意识到，很多事情都被
thrown on the back burner and is no
搁置一边，
longer important because
不再重要了，因为
you're [__] getting older and some
你他妈的年纪大了，有些
[__] just isn't isn't the same, right?
事情已经不一样了，对吧？
Like I just made a decision to let go of
就像我刚刚决定放弃
a certain version of life and embrace my
某种生活方式，拥抱我的
age and all the fun that comes with it.
年龄以及随之而来的所有乐趣。   那么，
&gt;&gt; What about being a man? It's it's
做个男人又如何呢？ 这真让人
confusing. I think it's more confusing
困惑。 我认为
than ever for many to be a man. And we
对很多人来说，做男人比以往任何时候都更加令人困惑。 我们
often talk about this masculinity crisis
经常谈到这种男性气质危机，即
where men have less men male friends
男性拥有的男性朋友
than ever before. Um the stats are
比以往任何时候都少。 嗯，
pretty shocking on this. The suicide
这方面的统计数据相当令人震惊。 男性
suicidation is 300 to 400% higher in
自杀率比女性高 300% 至 400%
men. There's a college degree gap. For
。 存在大学学历差距。
degree in the women, three in the US,
在美国，每有两名男性获得学士学位，就有
three women do. There's a workforce
三名女性获得学士学位。 劳动力
dropout rate, which is pretty
流失率相当高，这很
terrifying. Millions of prime age men
可怕。 数百万年龄在
between the age of 24 and 50 are no
24 岁至 50 岁之间的黄金年龄段男性已
longer in the labor force, representing
不再属于劳动力市场，劳动力
an almost 10% drop.
下降了近 10%。
&gt;&gt; Um, being a man is tough these days
嗯，如今做男人真不容易，
&gt;&gt; for a bunch of different reasons.
原因有很多。
&gt;&gt; You got a plethora
你有很多很多事情，但这并不
straightforward.
简单明了。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yes. polluted waters is what I call it.
。 我称之为污染水体。
Extremely polluted waters.
水体污染极其严重。
&gt;&gt; What advice have you got for for young
对于年轻男性，你有什么建议，比如
men on in terms of like what it takes to
如何才能
be a a good man?
成为一个好男人？
&gt;&gt; You know, I think the definition of a of
你知道吗，我觉得
a good man is so foggy today.
如今好人的定义非常模糊。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; Right. [clears throat] And
正确的。  [清嗓子]
I'm a firm believer that change comes
我坚信改变需要
within time. [clears throat] So I'll
时间。  [清嗓子] 所以，
start by saying that and I understand
首先我要说的是，我知道
that you know
你也明白一切都不
nothing should stay the same.
应该一成不变。
Everything should evolve
万物皆应在
when it's evolving. The conversation of
进化过程中进化。
a of a man and what makes a man a man is
关于男人以及是什么造就了男人的讨论很
weird. It's like
奇怪。 感觉
&gt;&gt; it's not evolving right. And you know, I
它的发展方向不太对劲。 你知道，我从小就接受的是
a leader or leadership. And I think, you
领导者或领导力方面的熏陶。 我想，愿
know, rest in peace to my dad.
我父亲安息。
It's [__] up of a road that my dad
我爸那条路糟透了
had.
。
My dad's like later years
我父亲晚年的生活
were driven from accountability.
动力源于责任感。
I'm aware of what I didn't do. I'm aware
我知道我没做什么。 我意识到自己
of the mistakes that I made and I'm
犯了哪些错误，也
aware of what I should have did much
意识到自己本应该做得更好
better. I can't change those things, but
。 我无法改变那些事情，但
I would love to try to be the best
我很想努力成为最好的
grandfather
祖父
or grandparent that I can be.
或祖父母。
Kevin,
凯文，
I love you and I love your brother, but
我爱你，我也爱你的哥哥，但
I can't go back. I can only say I'm
我回不去了。 我只能说声
sorry
抱歉，
and I wish I could. You don't have to.
我真希望我能帮上忙。 你不必这样做。
Like, the grandkids are your focus. And
比如，你的重心都放在孙辈身上。
if you can be the dopest example of a
如果你能成为
grandpop to them,
他们心目中最棒的爷爷榜样，那
then that's the win for me at this
对我来说就是最大的胜利了
point. But his accountability in that
。 但那一刻他所展现出的责任感，
moment is what I remember the most about
是我记忆中最深刻、
my father and love the most. Because
最爱我的父亲。 因为
leadership or lack thereof
领导层的缺失或领导层的缺失，
put me in a position to say I don't want
让我不得不说我不想
to do that.
做这件事。
I want to do
我想做
this. And not because my dad is like the
这件事。 倒不是因为我爸有多
worst, but [__] man, if he didn't do
糟糕，但老天，如果他没把
these things wrong, back to tying [__]
这些事情做错，回到正题
in, I wouldn't know how to do them
，我都不知道该怎么把事情做好
right. Mhm.
。 嗯。
&gt;&gt; So now I got two boys. I want to make
现在我有两个儿子了。 我想
sure that my example
确保我给儿子们树立的榜样是：
leadership, responsibility,
领导力、责任感、
it's accountability,
担当、
&gt;&gt; emotions,
情感。
&gt;&gt; you know, I'm not against emotions, but
你知道，我并不反对情感，
but I am also I am a student of
但我也明白
everybody has problems.
每个人都会遇到问题。
Nobody there's not a shortage of
那里的人谁都不缺
problems. So the weight of the world
问题。 所以，
that you feel is the heaviest for you
你感受到的最沉重的世界重量，
may not come close to what the weight of
可能远不及
the world is for you. And I think in
世界对你而言真正的重量。 我认为，
sharing your emotions and having an
分享你的情绪并有
opportunity to voice or offload them
机会表达或倾诉它们
extremely important but you also in a
非常重要，但你也
world where you know weakness can at
知道，在这个世界上，弱点
some point in time be taken advantage
有时会被人利用
of. Right?
。 正确的？
and and sharks as I presented earlier.
正如我之前提到的，你身处一个充满猎物和鲨鱼的世界。
And it's it doesn't mean that your
但这并不意味着你的
emotions don't matter because they do.
情绪不重要，因为它们很重要。
It means that you also have to be smart
这意味着你也必须聪明机智
and aware, right? And what are you
，对吧？ 你
ultimately trying your best to become?
最终努力想成为什么样的人？
And what are you ultimately trying to be
你最终想要成为什么样的
the best example for yourself first and
榜样？首先是为了自己，
then others for?
其次是为了他人？
I don't mind being weak, but I talk to
我不介意自己软弱，但我会和
my kids. I talk to them in our voice.
孩子们谈谈。 我用我们的声音和他们交谈。
Your dad deals with struggles that
你爸爸正在经历
you'll never know about because I don't
你永远不会知道的困难，因为我不想让
want you to have to feel the burden of
你感受到他的负担
them. It's my job to try my best to make
。 我的工作就是尽我所能让
life easier for you so that you can go
你的生活更轻松，这样你就能取得比
on and do way more than I ever have.
我更大的成就。
It's my job to give you the
我的工作就是给你提供
opportunities to learn [__] that I never
机会，让你学习到我这个
knew that I could learn at this stage.
阶段从未想过自己能学到的东西。
But I'm going to make sure that I
但我会确保我与你的
communicate with you differently than I
沟通方式与你之前与我的
was communicated with. I'm not going to
沟通方式不同。 我不会
let you [__] off or take advantage of
让你溜之大吉，也不会让你滥用
your fingertips. I'm not going to let
你手头现有的资源。 我不会让
you tell me the things that you think
你凭感觉告诉我
you should do because you feel when I
你应该做什么，而我
know right now at this stage in your
知道在你
life what's best for you.
人生的这个阶段，什么才是对你最好的。
That's my format of parenting and it
这是我的育儿方式，但这
doesn't mean it's the same for others.
并不意味着其他人也适用。
But for the man that I am,
但就我而言，根据我自身的经历，
I know the type of man that I want my
我知道我希望我的孩子成为什么样的人
was and is. And I think that if I
。 我认为，如果我能
correctly position them to simply
正确地引导他们
understand in your older age, you make
理解，到了老年，你可以做
whatever decisions you want. I'm your
任何你想做的决定。 我是你
father. I'm gonna love you regardless.
父亲。 无论如何，我都会爱你。
Has no care worry to me. I want to know
对我来说，他完全不用担心。 我想知道
that I did my job for what I was
我是否尽职尽责地做好了我负责的事情
supposed to control. And I want to know
。 我想知道
that our conversations and our dialogue
我们之间的谈话和对话是否
was always straight up and
始终坦诚
straightforward enough to where you were
直率，让你感到
comfortable to talk to me and you were
自在地与我交谈，让你感到
comfortable and feeling like your father
自在，并让你觉得你的父亲会为你好
has your best interest. That's for me
。 这
that's my makeup. And in a time today,
就是我的妆容。 如今，
my makeup doesn't have to fit yours. And
我的妆容不必与你的相符。
I'm okay with that. And I'm okay with
我对此并不介意。 我完全接受
yours being whatever it is for you. But
你的选择，无论它对你来说是什么。 但
I think we're in a time today where
我认为，我们如今所处的时代，
society wants to fight with one another
社会上充斥着太多互相争吵的情绪
about it's it's just too much of like,
，
well, if you don't see it my way, then
比如，如果你不认同我的观点，那
you're dumb.
你就是个傻瓜。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; And and that's I think that's why the
而我认为，这就是为什么这场
conversation has gotten so inconsistent
对话变得如此前后矛盾
and polluted.
、充满争议的原因。
That's my personal opinion and my side
那是我个人的观点以及我所掌握的
of information attached to it. So
信息。 所以
hopefully, you know, your viewers can
，我希望你的观众能够
hear that and understand that and know
听到并理解这一点，并且知道他们
it's okay with not being okay with my
不接受我的
choice.
选择也是可以的。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
That's okay.
没关系。
&gt;&gt; Kevin, we have a closing tradition where
凯文，我们有个结束仪式的传统，
the last guest leaves a question for the
最后一位客人会给下一位客人留下一个问题
next, not knowing who they're leaving it
，但他并不知道这个问题是留给谁的
for. The question left for you is, what
。 留给你的问题是：
is the advice you got as an adult that
作为成年人，你得到的哪条建议
had the most significant impact on your
对你的人生影响最大
life?
？
&gt;&gt; I'm going to go to best the best piece
我要说的最好的
of advice came from Chris Rock where
建议来自克里斯·洛克，
Chris Rock told me early in my comedy
克里斯·洛克在我喜剧生涯早期就告诉过我
career. He says his exact word is you
。 他说他的原话是，你
don't just want to make [__] laugh.
不能只是单纯地想逗黑人笑。
the world is so much bigger than your
世界远比你所在的
block or your neighborhood. He said,
街区或社区大得多。 他说：
"Get out the country. Get out the
“走出这个国家。走出这个
country and figure out a way to make the
国家，想办法让
world laugh and comedy will be so much
全世界都开怀大笑，喜剧就会变得
better."
更好。”
At that point, I was very like specific
那时，我
in my material.
对素材的要求非常具体。
15, you know, we got these
15，你知道，我们买到这些东西的时候，
the this drugstore is crazy. YOU EVER
这家药店简直疯了。 你
HAD A GUY IN THE DRUGSTORE IN YOUR
家附近药店里有没有那种男的
BLOCK? AND IT'S LIKE, WELL, everybody
？ 感觉就像，嗯，每个人都
doesn't relate or can't relate. How do
无法感同身受，或者说无法感同身受。 如何
you broaden it? How do you how do you
扩大它的范围？ 你如何才能
open it up so that you're never changing
敞开心扉，同时又不改变
your material or who you are? Everywhere
你的创作内容或你自身的本质？ 无论
you go in the world, people can laugh
你走到世界哪个角落，人们都会开怀大笑，
and you never have to adjust. Get out
你永远不需要做出任何调整。 离开
the country.
这个国家。
Get bigger in the way you're thinking
拓宽你
about
对
your craft.
技艺的思考方式。
&gt;&gt; I mean, you've done that across the
我的意思是，你
board and across industries now. you've
现在已经在各个领域、各个行业都做到了这一点。 你
been willing to be the person, the
一直甘愿做那个
outsider in lots of rooms. That seems to
在很多场合都显得格格不入的局外人。 这似乎
be really central to your success. And
对你的成功至关重要。
what Chris Chris Rock said to you there
克里斯·洛克当时对你说的话就是：
was get out into the unfamiliar. Go put
走出去，去探索未知领域。 去
yourself in an unfamiliar place. And
一个陌生的地方。
when I look at your career and the
当我回顾你的职业生涯以及
empire that you've been able to build
你在
across business and investing, it's
商业和投资领域建立起来的庞大帝国时，我发现事实正是
exactly that. It's you were willing to
如此。 是你
be in unfamiliar territories for some
出于某种原因愿意身处陌生的领域
reason.
。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. Yeah. You know what you just made
。 是的。 你知道你刚才的话也让
me think about too and and I I want to
我想到了什么，而且我想在
backtrack before we leave. One thing
我们离开之前把话说清楚。 有一件事感觉有点
kind of crazy just when you were talking
疯狂，就像你刚才在谈论
about the conversation of men, like it's
男性话题时，
a weird thing that's happening where you
发生了一件很奇怪的事情，那就是有些
do have men that are opening up more and
男性开始更加敞开心扉，
talking more about like the struggles
更多地谈论他们的困境。
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; of a man,
对于一个男人来说，
but then those things are like
这些话就像是
being used against them in the
在
conversation of a man. Like when you get
男人的谈话中被用来对付他们一样。 就像当你开始
to talking about like the things that
谈论
you're dealing with and the emotion and
你正在处理的事情、情绪以及
&gt;&gt; the mental health
心理
&gt;&gt; the mental health and the weight like it
健康、体重等问题时，似乎
seems that in this time today more men
在当今时代，越来越多的男性
are being forward and wanting to express
开始主动表达
and talk but the fear of being judged
和谈论这些事情，但又害怕
after.
事后被评判。
&gt;&gt; Do you have that fear?
你有这种恐惧吗？
&gt;&gt; No, I don't I don't get [__] I don't
不，我什么都得不到。 我不太
really I don't really care too much what
在意
people think.
别人怎么想。
&gt;&gt; Have you struggled with your mental
你是否曾受过心理
health?
健康方面的困扰？
&gt;&gt; No.
不，
&gt;&gt; No. I think I told you my [__] is like
不。我想我已经跟你说过，我的情况越来越糟，
more more stress. It's not a struggle.
压力越来越大。 这并不难。
It's like
这就像，
&gt;&gt; Is that anxiety or is it is it
那是焦虑吗？还是……
&gt;&gt; No, just like I know I do too much.
不，就像我知道我做得太多了一样。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。   我确信无疑
&gt;&gt; Like I know I know I know for a fact.
。   那
&gt;&gt; What's the symptom of that? How do you
是什么症状？ 你
feel? Like
感觉如何？ 就像
&gt;&gt; you have to like you have to shut down.
你必须……就像你必须关机一样。
So like what I'm getting better at is in
所以，我现在做得越来越好的一点是，
a day there's time I just don't I'm off
一天中总有那么一些时间，我不会一直
the phone. I got it. I know I told him I
打电话。 我得到了它。 我知道我跟他说过我
would do calls. Just tell them I'll
会打电话。 你就告诉他们我
start that tomorrow or the day after.
明天或后天开始做。
But like there's a there's a time where
但有时候，
I get to a point in the day where I'm
一天中总有那么几个时刻，我会觉得
like, "Okay, that oh that's it for me.
，“好了，够了，我不想再说了。
&gt;&gt; You're done.
结束了。我的……
&gt;&gt; That's my Yeah. Like and I'm I'm
是的。我真的受够了。
literally I'm done. I don't want to I
我
don't want to talk about anything else.
不想再谈任何其他事情。
I don't want to I don't want to hear."
我不想听。”
&gt;&gt; So you're pushing yourself right up to
所以你一次又一次地把自己逼到
the edge over and over and over and over
极限
again.
。
&gt;&gt; I get to a a point in a day and that
一天中，我总会有那么一个时间点，那就是我关机的时间，而且这个时间点越来越早。
before it was, you know, we hours of the
以前，我常常要到深夜好几个小时，还在
night and I'm still on the phone
打电话
figuring it out. and all day you just
解决问题。 你一整天都在
been racing and racing and racing. So I
比赛、比赛、比赛。 所以我
think the older that I've gotten. I've
觉得，随着年龄的增长，我越来越…… 我
realized more and more that's not
越来越意识到这样做是
healthy.
不健康的。
The healthy side comes with silence for
健康的做法是
a sec. Like you need you need some you
短暂的沉默。 就像你需要
need some silence. A ride in a car by
一些安静的时候一样。 独自驾车
yourself, no music.
，不放音乐。
&gt;&gt; Sounds a bit like a disease.
听起来有点像某种疾病。
&gt;&gt; No, you need silence.
不，你需要安静。
&gt;&gt; Do you know what I mean by it sounds a
你知道我说的“听起来
bit like a disease? Because this is
有点像某种疾病”是什么意思吗？ 因为这
something that's taking you to a point
件事会把你带到一个让
where it's like it's kind of hurting you
你感觉有点痛苦的地步
a little bit. and I can relate. So, it's
。 我感同身受。 所以，
not like I'm like passing judgment
我并不是在评判你，
because you just described my entire
因为你刚才描述的正是我的
life.
人生。
&gt;&gt; Um, you're not going to be as present
嗯，你可能无法像以前那样陪伴
with your loved ones. You're not going
你的家人了。 你将无法像以前那样
to be as present in your relationship. I
全身心投入到这段感情中。 我
know you're married. Um, you've got four
知道你已婚。 嗯，你有四个
kids. How how are you ever going to be
孩子。
like truly present when your brain is
当你的大脑
like,
想着
&gt;&gt; "Yes,
“是的，
but also, how do you how do you become
但是，你如何才能坦然接受
comfortable with being okay with people
别人
not understanding?"
不理解你”的时候，你又该如何才能真正活在当下呢？
That's the trick. Like, I I hate to say
这就是诀窍。 说实话，我不太想
it bluntly.
直说。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. I used to have such a high level
。 我以前非常在意
of give a [__] attached to how you felt
你对我做出的那些对我
about my decisions that were best for
最有利的决定有何感想
me. Oh god, I don't want to say cuz
。 天哪，我不想说，因为
they're going to feel like I'm not doing
他们会觉得我没尽力，那可就太
it's going to be crazy. I don't [sighs]
疯狂了。 我不（叹气）
I'll just do it
我会这么做的，
because I'm thinking more about you than
因为我更多地想到的是你而不是
I'm thinking about me, right? I'm
我自己，对吧？ 我把
putting everybody before me. I'm putting
大家都放在第一位。 我把
everybody's needs, everybody's wants,
每个人的需求、每个人的愿望、
everybody's reasons all before me.
每个人的理由都放在首位。
Nobody is thinking about the volume of
没有人会去想
that I'm delivering on a day-to-day
我每天要说多少台词，
and how much of that like happens over
以及有多少台词是反复出现的
and over again. Nobody's thinking about
。 没人会想到这件事
it. So the day that I became comfortable
。 所以，当我能坦然接受
with going I don't really give a [__] if
去那里的时候，我就真的不在乎
like they understand or not. Like I'm
他们是否理解了。 我觉得我
done. I know but they feel it's really
做完了。 我知道，但他们觉得这真的很
important. You got to do it today. I'll
重要。 你今天必须做完。 我
talk to them tomorrow. Nothing's going
明天会和他们谈谈。 什么都不会
to happen. Nothing's going to change
发生。
from this time to that time. You have to
从现在到那时，一切都不会改变。 你必须
get to a point to where you actually get
达到这样的境界：真正理解
that and are okay with that because if
这一点，并且接受这一点，
not, you're constantly putting all of
否则，你就会不断地把
the [__] from outside there on your
外面的糟心事都放到你的
table and like your plate's always full.
桌子上，就像你的盘子总是满满的。
You're never finishing your [__]
你永远也吃不完你那该死的
plate because you're just constantly
盘子里的东西，因为总
people just keep coming and dumping more
有人不断地往你盘子里倒更多的
[__] on it. So imagine that. Imagine
垃圾。 想象一下。 想象一下，
people just keep telling you keep
人们一直告诉你继续
eating. You just keep getting full. like
吃。 你总是感觉吃饱了。 就像
eventually you can't [__] breathe and
最后你他妈的喘不过气来，然后就
you bust. It's no different from your
崩溃了。 这和你的想法没什么不同
from your mind. And and and more today
。 而且，而且，如今因
from mental overload, man. Like people
精神超负荷而崩溃的人比以往任何时候都多。 好像人们
aren't crazy. I hate the like this whole
都没疯似的。 我讨厌这种
crazy. You crazy [__] You
疯狂的感觉。 你这个疯子。 你
crazy. It's like [__] are just
疯了。 就像那些混蛋吃
popping like it's too much and they
太多东西，突然就爆发了，他们吃
[__] when they snack they snap.
零食的时候就突然发作。   就是这样。
That's it. That's not what I'M SAYING.
我不是那个意思。
I'M [__] I'M SICK a check like
我他妈都快吐了，
goddamn man you crazy. No, you're not.
老兄你疯了吧。 不，你不是。
[__] just popped.
那帮混蛋突然就爆了。
&gt;&gt; But you could you got the money to go
但是如果你有钱的话，完全可以去
chill in Bali.
巴厘岛放松一下。
&gt;&gt; I'm going I I
我要去，
&gt;&gt; But but you don't
但是你没有，
&gt;&gt; I have the money to not go chill in
我有钱不去放松一下
body. I have the money to say I'm not
。 我有足够的钱说我
talking anymore today.
今天不再说话了。
That's the That's the difference. It's
这就是区别所在。 这与
not about the vacation. It's not about
度假无关。 重点不在于
the trip. It's not about I'm not talking
旅行本身。 重点不是我今天不再说话了
anymore today. So the people and the
。 所以，
resources that I put around me to help
我安排在我身边的人员和资源来帮助
me do your job. What happens next for
我完成你的工作。 接下来你会经历什么
you? We sit here in 10 years time, it
？ 十年后，我们坐在这里，一切都很
all went well. What happened?
顺利。 发生了什么？
&gt;&gt; I think in 10 years time, if I'm able to
我想，10 年后，如果我能
sit on a stool
坐在
at a comedy club with 30 people and do
一个有 30 个人的喜剧俱乐部的凳子上，表演
material and enjoy my craft,
段子，享受我的技艺，
and it's little small hole-in-the-wall
而且是在那种不起眼的小
comedy clubs, wherever I'm living at the
喜剧俱乐部里，无论我当时住在哪里
time, and I do it maybe twice a week.
，我可能每周表演两次。
and I golf. Uh, and I spend time with my
我喜欢打高尔夫。 嗯，我会花时间陪伴我的
kids and hopefully their kids and I'm a
孩子们，希望也能陪伴他们的孩子们。我是个
grandpop and we're able to like look
爷爷，我们可以一起翻看以前的
through photo albums of remember when
相册，回忆过去的点点滴滴。
I've built that are operating and
我建造的、能够自主运行和
functioning on its own.
运作的东西，也需要一些捐款。
That's
这就是
that's my version [clears throat] of
我理解的成功（清嗓子）
success.
。
&gt;&gt; Kevin, thank you.
凯文，谢谢你。
&gt;&gt; Thank you, man. Thank you so much for
谢谢你，兄弟。 非常感谢你之前
all the um you talked about how you've
说的那些话，比如你如何
made people's lives happier and uh made
让人们的生活更幸福，如何让
people more connected etc. And that's
人们之间的联系更紧密等等。而这
exactly the impact you've had on me. I
正是你对我产生的影响。 我
remember the first time I I watched one
记得第一次看
of your uh comedy specials and watched
你的喜剧特辑，第一次看
you on stage was when I was going
你在舞台上的表演，那是
through a very tough part of my life. I
我人生中一段非常艰难的时期。 我
was lonely. I was in this room in
感到孤独。 我当时就在曼彻斯特的这个房间里
Manchester. I'm probably 18 years old at
。 我当时大概 18 岁，
the time and I'm trying to figure out my
正在努力规划我的
career and my future and things are hard
事业和未来，生活很艰难，
and I think like pirating your pirating
我觉得盗版
your comedy specials was that little
你的喜剧特辑就像是那短暂的
moment of escapism. It was that little
逃避现实的时刻。 那是
moment of joy in my day and so you're
我一天中短暂的快乐时光，所以对于数以
that for so many many millions of people
百万计
that you'll never get to meet. You
你永远不会遇到的人来说，你就是那份快乐时光。 你
brought so much joy to families. You
给许多家庭带来了欢乐。 你
brought families together. You brought
让家庭团聚。 你带
me and my girlfriend out to come and see
我和我的女朋友去
you in the Royal Albert Hall and also
皇家阿尔伯特音乐厅看过你的演出，
I've seen you in New York City when you
我还看过你在纽约市的演出，我记得好像是在
did I think it was Madison Square Garden
麦迪逊广场花园的
here as well on that square stage. It's
那个方形舞台上。
you're a source of joy and connectivity
你是快乐和联结的源泉，
and if the world ever needed that energy
如果说世界此刻最需要这种能量，那么
right right now, um it needs it now more
现在比以往任何时候都更需要
than ever.
。
&gt;&gt; I humbly appreciate you and thank you.
我由衷地感谢您。
Uh this was amazing, man. And I and I
哇，这太棒了！ 我
think you're doing a service of good and
认为你做了一件好事，
what you're providing for the masses is
你为大众提供的服务是
is necessary. So don't stop. Keep going,
必要的。 所以不要停下来。 继续加油，
man.
兄弟。
&gt;&gt; Thank you so much. All right.
太感谢了。 好的。
&gt;&gt; Thank you so much. Appreciate it,
太感谢了。 谢谢你，
brother.
兄弟。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Make sure you keep what I'm about to say
请务必将我接下来要说的话藏在心里
to yourself. I'm inviting 10,000 of you
。 我邀请你们中的 10,000 人
to come even deeper into the diary of a
更深入地了解一位 CEO 的日记
CEO. Welcome to my inner circle. This is
。 欢迎来到我的核心圈子。 这是
a brand new private community that I'm
我即将向全世界推出的一个全新的私人社区
launching to the world. We have so many
。 我们这里发生了很多
incredible things that happen that you
不可思议的事情，但你却
are never shown. We have the briefs that
从未见过。
are on my iPad when I'm recording the
我在录制对话时，iPad 上会显示一些简要说明
conversation. We have clips we've never
。 我们有一些从未
released. We have behindthe-scenes
公开过的视频片段。 我们有
conversations with the guests and also
与嘉宾的幕后访谈，还有从未
released. and so much more. In the
公开过的剧集。 还有更多。 在这个
circle, you'll have direct access to me.
圈子里，你可以直接联系到我。
You can tell us what you want this show
您可以告诉我们您希望这个节目
to be, who you want us to interview, and
成为什么样子，您希望我们采访谁，以及
the types of conversations you would
您
love us to have. But remember, for now,
希望我们进行哪些类型的对话。 但请记住，目前
we're only inviting the first 10,000
我们只邀请前 10,000 名
people that join before it closes. So,
加入的人，活动即止。 所以，
if you want to join our private closed
如果您想加入我们的私人封闭
community, head to the link in the
社区，请点击
description below or go to
下方说明中的链接或访问
daccircle.com.
daccircle.com。   到时候
I will speak to you then.
我再跟你谈。
Heat. Heat. [music]
热。 热。  [音乐]
[music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[唱歌]